Money, money, money. Hey!
ഉധ്‌ ഠ്ധ് റി. ലി!
You got a date with justice, One-Eyed Bart.
ദ്ധ ലഡ ദ്ന്ധ്യണ ധേപേണ്മോ.. 1:18 1-1::1-1-141॥
Too bad, Sheriff. I'm a married man.
ീലിനാ ടലി, ടല [1 111-1:118:1:1:111 11111
One-Eyed Betty!
8൦൬ ദലന്നമമട ടാഡ
I think you dropped something, mister.
ചവ ടാ ദ്വ ലലല ടടടധമഡ..
-Jessie? -Give it up, Bart!
-പിടെടില? ടല ഠി, ദാല്‌
You've reached the end of the line!
ദ്ധ ൭൨ 020൨ല്‍
l always wanted to go out with a bang!
11111111: :111:1 ഠി്ബലാദ്‌
-Oh, no! -The orphans!
00, റിറ്ലിധ! ്റലില്റര്സ്‌
Hate to leave early, but our ride is here.
ചവ ലാല നമ്്ലാല। ഗ്മ! 'ല്വാി ാലഹാമനിധവമ്ിയഖ്്‌ ൭൨ ടമ്വാലി
It's me or the kiddies, Sheriff. Take your pick.
1൩൭ മിവ ദ്ധ ലി്ഗഥല്ലധ, ടല... ബ്ല
Ride like the wind, Bullseye!
190 ഠി ലാട, ഒധിടലുട!
Hold him steady!
ലററ ഠി ഠ്ണബിധാധ്‌
Woody, hurry!
177000, ലോ
No!
11ഠിമിഠ
Glad I could catch the train!
ലേസ്പാഅമ മിവ ദ്ദ്വാമ ലിലഷലലഘാ!!
Now let's catch some criminals.
ട്ലിവ്ധമനാ മധ ഗ്മ യോ ല്ല
To infinity and beyond!
ലാമി ബ്ബ... ദ്ദ ടലബ്ധ്സയമ!
Reach for the sky.
6 1:111:111:]]7
You can't touch me, Sheriff!
ദ്ധ മിധാംില ടല മിവ.
I brought my attack dog with a built-in force field.
ചിവാദഥ ബന ലാബഘലമെ :111 11:11]:
Well, I brought my dinosaur who eats force-field dogs.
ചവ ലാമ ഠിനടം മിവ ൮9 നനദ ബന റാലിവമടടമ റമ
Evil Dr. Pork Chop!
൧. ൧0000 0൮9 ലന്‌
That's Mr. Evil Dr. Pork Chop to you.
1ധ 5൨. ലമണ ൧. ൧0൦00 1 മഠ വധ
“Buzz, shoot your laser at my badge.”
ഖമാ, (ല്പാല്ധ്മടല വല ാഠ്ദമ ൦൦ ലിവ.
“Woody, no. It'll kill you." "Just do it!"
77000, 01021. 19 ലിര്ബാധഥ്ധ്സത്വ.. ല്ഡിത്ഥ ടല്വ്മ!
“You're going to jail, Bart.” “Watch out!"
ദ്ധ മിഥ ണനടടധ്ലാല്ലയ, 83മ0.. 1120-02!
Mom!
ച്‌ി!
No, no, no. Just keep playing. Just pretend I'm not here.
11. "ലടിരബാലന്നമ്൩. മയി ലിവ ഖിദ്ദ ഠിട്ബ
Oh, no, Molly!
ഡി നീം
No, it's okay, Mom. It's a 50-foot baby from outer space.
12%, 2 ല്വാമ.. ബലാ 5 ൪0 ചി സാഗാ ഗഠ1രടമ
And she's on a rampage. Run for your lives!
ഉമ്ഥ റിമ ടലഠ്ദണാ നലറമസ്ധിം. 190 ടല്മനാിത്ഥ ഠി!
Buster, get out of there. Does the red light mean it's going?
ടല, ശധല മല ടമ്മ. ൧ഠഠവ്പാധ
Come on. Say "Happy birthday” to Molly.
കൃധി.. വല്വോദ്ഥ "ട്ടലിമണാല്ച്വി”ശഷ്വാാര്‍ം ഗീം
-Happy birthday! -Charming.
-ടല്മണമ്ദ്വഠി! -01, ലീാദ..!
-Look how tall you're getting. -Yeah!
1103ലാലയ്വാദ നാസേ ത്വ...
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
൧2൧22 1.7002ല7 ൧൭൧ ടല്‌ക്ഗദദ്ഥ്‌
“Good work, Buzz."
1ധറു3ട ാമറാധട, 8ധമമ..
Okay, places, everyone. Come on, come on. Get in position.
810ഖ, വാ ബ്ലാ, ടലസ്ഡാ ൦09! എഡി... ശബ ശദ്ധേധേത്ഥ
Wait! I can't find my other eye.
ധാ! വ്വ ലിം ദ്ദ്വാ ദേ ൩൭൭ മിവ ൮9 ടലാലല്‍ബി॥
-All right, whose foot's in my face? -It's mine. Give it back.
-8311091, ൭10 ടില്ാമ മഠ ന്ധി മിവ? ബ൭ ൩ മിവ.. ല്പാല॥ത്്തി
You have saved our lives. We are eternally grateful.
രവ ടലി ബമഗ യമബ്ി. ബി ലസ്ധത9 ധി ധാ ടല്മനബമ
Buzz! Mind if I squeeze in next to ya?
ഭധമമ! 8ഠ1ല൨ 2൭ മിവ ഠ്ധഠ്ധി ടലാല്ദന രഥ?
Yes. No. 1 mean, why would I mind squeezing next to you?
൫൭. നല ഗീല്ദ്ധ്‌ മിവ, ഭ്ലദ്വാ മിവ നലിലിഠ്ടമ ഡേ്ധി൦ ടലാല്ദ്വിര്ധ?
Is it hot in here?
൧ ലാട ഠിട്ബി?
Here they come!
1ധാധന ന്ഥി ദമാ!
Sarge, you got it?
ടാലി, ദ്ധ ൭൨ ദ്ലാദ്ധിബ്ബുര?
Mission accomplished.
നീടി ടലിലടമി..
Careful. Careful!
1120-02.. 1120-00
All right, guys. We got one shot at this. Everyone ready?
8110൨, ദ്ധ ൦൦. അ ഠ്ദ 1 ലാല്ധമറാ ധഴിധ്ബി. ടലസ്ഡദ ൦09 റ ടലി?
We're ready, Woody. Let's do it!
ബി ദമ ടലറി൭.. സൃഡ്ില്ഡിര്യ
Okay, Buzz. Make the call.
810൨, 8ധമമ.. ല്വിത്ലാണാഠ॥ിദല്‍്‌
Target is on approach.
ടട ടല്ദററ നലാന്വാ..
Just like we rehearsed it, guys.
ടന ടലാലന്‍ി ൮ 1൭ ലാലി, ദ്വ ൦09..
Hello?
ലിം?
Hello? Anyone there?
ലിം? ൧0൭ ടലടില്വാ റി ടമ്മ?
Molly, stay out of my room!
ഗം[ദപധ്വ്ത്ഥ ദല മോ 0॥॥ലയ്‌
I wasn't in your room.
ചവ മ ണടടധിലാ॥॥ലത്ധ
Then who was messing with my stuff?
ദ്രിദ്ധാല്റി്ഡ ടില്യാമ ൮9 ദ്വധേധാമമററ മിവ?
It wasn't me.
ബര ലാധിത്ഥ മിവ...
Well, that went well.
1ധവാലില്വ ഠ്ണബാറട..
He held me! He actually held me!
11:11 :1:111:1:11]! 019 ടലാലാബസ്ൂമ നന മിഡ്‌
This is just sad.
൨, ബി ടാ നബി.
Who we kiddin’? The kid's 17 years old.
[പ്രമ മി ണലബ്വാധ ടില്വാമ? 8ധദ്ക്ല്ധ ഠ്മ്ഡാലനഥ 17 മഥ
We ain't ever gettin’ played with.
൭ ലിറത്ഥ നല ്ബോന്മ 1൭91..
Guys, hey, hold up.
ദ്ധ മ, നല, ഡന9േ.. [പമ ലാലിധിത്ഥ നടുയലമ ട്‌
We need a staff meeting. Everyone! A staff meeting!
ടലസ്ഡാ ൦0! ഗീടടുധമ ടല
Not again!
110൭16 ടല്യി। 91!
Come on. Slink, gather everyone up.
ചൃഡധി.. ടബപവ്വാധിത്ഥ ടലസ്ധ മാ
We are gathered, Woody.
ബി റ്മ്൩ാലിഡസ്വാധി ഗ൦൦൨..
Okay. First off,
ലമാ ടലധ॥,
we all knew Operation Playtime was a long shot.
ഗ്മ ടലസ്ധാ ്ധ ല്രാലടടി ലദൃഷ്നം 'ലിധാല്ധാല്ുപത
More like a misfire.
1ലാ॥൨ ടലാലല്‍ി ലാമി.
But we've always said this job isn't about getting played with. It's about...
ചവ ൭ ടല്ല്ധ ത്മ ഡാടട ബി ധിരന രാമടി ലാലന്നമ്ന ബര ൭൩൭൧൭..
Being there for Andy. We know.
ഒലി റി ടാ ധി... യി ദധി
But we can try again! Right?
1പ്മവാഠിലി ധോ ടലരി।॥ മഠ! ദധി?
I'm callin’ it, guys. We're closing up shop.
ചവ നമിറ നബ്ലമ യി,ത്വ ംമാ.. [വര ലിത്ഥ ലിസ.
What?
൧്പാമ?
Andy's going to college any day now. That was our last shot.
൧൨൦0 മിഥ 1 രില്‍ ാ॥13-10119 നമടമ. 1ധാല്ധാമററ ലലിമ്പാന്മ
We're going into attic mode, folks.
[പമ ലിദ്ഥ നടടധിഠ ന്‌ 10൦0൭, ദ്വ ൦൭0..!
Keep your accessories with you at all times.
ഉമടിവ്ഥ മിദടടംി ദ്വസ്ധവലാലമഠ്ദ ര്‍്ബിരസ്ധ ടലാദബ്ന ണമടടാ
Spare parts, batteries, anything you need for an orderly transition.
ചീറി ബ്ദ, വാലി, ല്വാദ ടദ്വദ ൮9 ദ്ധ ാലിധിത്ഥ ധ0 ടിടി ദ ലഡഡ
Orderly? Don't you get it? We're done! Finished! Over the hill!
ലയഡാ ദ്ധ ഖിന്ലമണ? [പ്ര റ ബ്വടമല്‍! ലാട! നലിപ്ധ ഡല
Hey, hey, hey, now. Come on, guys. We all knew this day was coming.
റല, ഥി! ഷഡി, ത്വ ൦09.. [പ്ര ടലസ്ധമ മധ നമ ബി ലിര്ഥ ധാമ
Yeah, but now it's here.
൮൫൭.. ഖാ ടലി [ബ൭ ഠ്ല ടവ്വല്‍
Look, every toy goes through this. No one wants to see...
ട്ലിച്ാ നമ്മ നലല്ധ്സത. 121 ഠി ട॥ല്വാ 3 നമ.
Hey, Sarge! What are you doing?
റല, ടലി! ഡാ ദ്ധ ധാ
War's over, folks. Me and the boys are moving on.
ലററ ൭0 ണമ... ചവ റ്ദബാധഠ്ല്പാധ്ടല്ത്ഥ ബടിത്ഥ
-Moving on? -You're going AWOL?
ല്ലാ? ര്മധ മിര ൮൭ഠ ൧ഥ൦?
We done our duty. Andy's grown up.
ബി ദ്ദ ടലിടടലിമറ ഡാടട യമി. ൧൧൦ റല ലാടടമ..
And let's face it, when the trash bags come out,
1ദ്ദ്വാ ബര്യാഥ, 0॥മാ9്റഠ ടബ്വാ ഠി॥ഷ്ധലിര്ഥ..
we army guys are the first to go.
10൭ മാ ടിന ല്ത്ഥ വാധ്വ
-Trash bags? -Who said anything about trash bags?
ഒല ട്വാമ?
It has been an honor serving with you. Good luck, folks.
11:11) 11:11: 11111111: ദി ദ്ധ. ടണം ലാലിയ, ദ്ധ നാ
You're gonna need it.
ദ്ധ മി ാലിധിത്ബ..
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait!
12%, ചല. സനാ
-We're getting thrown away? -No. No one's getting thrown away.
രി മിത്ഥ വധ? “1210 മഠ ടില്വാ ൮9 മിത്ഥ വധ
How do you know?
ദാഠുഖ്നാനാ ദ്ധ മധ
-We're being abandoned! -We'll be fine, Jessie.
1:11: 1111111111: 5:11] 11 മിദ്ഥ ലാലി ടല, ഒലടടില..
-So why did Sarge leave? -Should we leave?
-ിമഠി। ഗ്വാ ട്മ്ബലാലഠി? 11ലധടിര്ന്മാലി?
-I thought we were goin’ to the attic. -I hate all this uncertainty!
ചവ നാന മിത്ഥ ദ 1ലഘ..
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on now. Wait a minute. Quiet!
ധാ ഠ്ധ്ധ.. സ്ഥാ ഷ്ലാ.. സ്‌
No one's getting thrown out, okay? We're all still here.
121 ഠി ടില്വാ 9 മഥ 0100൭9. [പ്ര ടലസ്ധമ നമട്വാലയഠ്ദ ഠിട്ബ
I mean, yeah, we've lost friends along the way.
സിലിദ്ധഠ്‌ മിവ, ൭, റ്൭ ശ്വേ ഗ്യ ടലാബുദന ടട
-Wheezy and Etch and... -Bo Peep?
“770൯ലെ 0 50 ദ്ദ0.. -8ഠ ലലാ?
Yeah. Even Bo.
൫൭.. ഒം ധാ.
All good toys who've gone on to new owners.
ടലസ്ഡാ ണനല്നമബാമേട ഈ ദ്ലാലിത്ഥ ാഠ്ദ ലാലാല
But through every yard sale, every spring cleaning, Andy held on to us!
ച്വാ। നല്ല്ധി്‌ ടലില്വ്ധമി്ദില്ംനു... ..ടലിദ്വാ ാലമ്പാലടി മഥ ഡനമ,
He must care about us, or we wouldn't be here.
൧019 (ലല ടമാത്ബിന്മ ഒല ന്മ മാലി ഠിട്ബ
You wait. Andy's gonna tuck us in the attic. It'll be safe and warm...
ദ്ധ ഡാ. ൧൧൦ മിത്ഥ നല്ദുന്സ്വാമഥ ന്മ ഠി 10൭0.
-And we'll all be together. -Exactly!
൧0 സ്൯ ടലസ്ധാ മി്ബാലടമണമ.. ലാമ ടല്യി॥!
There's games up there, and books, and...
൧03 ലാലനല്വമറ ഠി മട ടമ ദ്മാധിവപാധിവ. ൧൭൨..
-The racecar track! -The racecar track. Thank you!
1ലീധിഷലര ാലിധ്പാമമ്‌!
-And the old TV. -There you go, the old TV.
൧0 ലിലധ്ടുറ മണ. 1 ഠി൭, ലിലധിടു ന മന൩൭..
And those guys from the Christmas decorations box. They're fun, right?
ഉമ്ഥ നല ദ്ദ രല ലട ഗ്ര്ടണടട. [010 നബ്ഘലംനംദത്ബാധിത്ന?
And someday, if we're lucky, Andy may have kids of his own.
ഉമ ടമ മി, വീധ 1ന്൭ ാലനടട॥ ൦.
And he'll play with us then, right?
ഉമ്ഥ ഠി മിര ണമ ദി 1ന൯ നട ധവാധിത്ന?
We'll always be there for him.
[പര ലിദ്ഥ ടല്ല്ധാലമഠ്ട ഠിടമമ ധി.
Come on, guys. Let's get our parts together, get ready,
എഡ, ദ്വ ഗാ! ഡം, ന്൯ ധമ്ബാധിര്ഥ ടലന്ധമാമ്മാിബന്മലാലടാമണമ
and go out on a high note.
8ലടലഠിമ റിമ ഷ്ധല ദ ലാമ...
I'd better find my other eye.
81 ലിവ ല്ലി നമ മിവ 1191.
Where'd you leave it this time?
നീ ദ്ധ നാലി വി! ബ്?
Someplace dark. And dusty.
ടടധാഡ ല്പാമ൮9 ഠലിമാ.. ഉബാലണലാധി
Come on. Let's see how much we're going for on eBay.
നീച... ഡയ്പന്മ മലാലയ്വാ മാന്ധ ഠിന ലമ
Don't worry. Andy's gonna take care of us. I guarantee it!
പ്ല ലിടദ്ധ.. ൧൧൦ മിത്ഥ നല്ഖമഠമ 10൭.. ഷ്വ നലവ്ബസ്ന്സമ!
You guarantee it, huh?
ദ്ധ നല്പബിസ്ബമ, ദ?
I don't know, Buzz. What else could I say?
ഫ്വ മ ല്ഡ, ദധമമ.. ൧3 1൭ 0 ലി മിവ രവിര്ഥ?
Well, whatever happens, at least we'll all be together.
൧്വാ3 ടല്യ ൮9 ലാലിമല്വ,
For infinity and beyond.
8ധാബ്ബ് കേ ടല്ബ്ധ൪..
-Can I have your stereo? -No.
-8ഠ1ല ലവ മബ്പാ॥ ടലടം ദ്ധ? “11021.
-Why not? -'Cause I'm taking it with me.
1ലലല്വാ ദിലി -ടലാലാ മിവ മിത്ഥ നല്ബാമധമബത..
-Can I have your computer? -No.
-8ഠ1ലി ലിവ മബ്ാ॥ ്വാധ്ലത്ധ? “11021൦.
-Your video games? -Forget it, Molly.
-ലനല്നമറ ധിഠ്ലം വധ? ധാമ, 'റിഠ॥൮..
Okay. Andy, let's get to work here.
൧൧൦0, മധ ന്മ സ്ധിലിത്ഥ ലമ വ്ട്ബി..
Anything you're not taking to college either goes in the attic, or it's trash.
൧3 ടദ്യ ൮9 വ മിലാ 1൪ ശില...
-Mom, I'm not leaving till Friday. -Come on. It's garbage day.
12%, മിവ 'യിലാല। ടല ധേന... “1010091൩! 1൩൭ 0ല൨ ടബ്വാമി..
-Mom. -Look, it's simple.
1ബ൭ സ്ധ്ദവ.. ഉല്വാഥ 0ഠഠ്ദ, രില്‍...
Skateboard, college. Little League trophy, probably attic.
1000 1192 14൭൦, സ്ഥാന 1൦൦009..
Apple core, trash. You can do the rest.
8ചഠറ ലാമി, ടമ്പാമ1.. ദ്ധ വാല മിഡി ൮൭ ടലിലാസ്ബുര
Why do you still have these toys?
1ലദ്വാ ദ്ധ നട ണല്യ്പാമഥ നലനഥ ബി?
Molly, out of my room!
നിം ഘ്ധല ഠ്വ ല്ഡ്‌
Three more days and it's mine!
30 1൭9 ൦1൩൭ ബി ലിഡ്‌
Molly, you're not off the hook either.
ഗം ദ്ധ ഖി ലിലാമട..
You have more toys than you know what to do with.
ദ്ധ നലമസ്പാധസതി്‌ ലാ നല്ല ദമിയ ഠ്0ാലിധിത്ഥ
Some of them could make other kids really happy.
ടല്ലറമ റ്മ്സ രാംില്ഡാധമ്ിര്ഥ ാധഠില്ല്ലന ലബ്ബാ
What kids?
ധ്യ ണമ?
The children at the daycare. They're always asking for donations.
8ധഠ്മ്ലാധഠ്ല്ം ദ്വാധടാലാബമാമമ.. ദിലലയ ടല്ല്ധ സ്ന ഠ്ലന്നമ..
What's daycare?
൧3 1ഡ ലധടമലാലവ്റുമമന? ടവ
-Mom. -No buts.
1210 റ്ദ '്വാ!..
You choose the toys you want to donate, I'll drop them off at Sunnyside.
ദ്ധ 1111 ണമ്നാണ യ ത്വ ലല ്ലേന്നമ.. മിവ മിഥ മലി ദ ട്ടി
Poor Barbie.
ടട ദദലാല..
I get the Corvette.
ച [1:േം
Andy, come on. You need to start making decisions.
൧൧൦0, വ ലാലിധ സ്ധിമവാധമഷ്വാധഡടമ..
Like what?
ടലാലി ദ്വാമ?
Like what are you gonna do with these toys?
൧3൮9 വ നമ്വാധമ€ നമ്മ ബി?
Should we donate them to Sunnyside?
1ബടിര് ന്മ നലഠ്ലന്നമബര ാഠ്ദ ട്ടി?
Mom, no one's gonna want those old toys.
121 ഠി ടില്വാ 30 ൭൧ ബത നമിറ നാ ബ്‌
They're junk.
സിലലയ ട്വാല..!
Fine. You have till Friday.
ചിറ ദ്ധ നലസ്വാധബത്ി നട വനാ ലി ധന.
Anything that's not packed for college or in the attic
൧3 ടദ്യ മ ഥി॥ഷ്ണടടിത്ഥ 1:11 1111]
-is getting thrown out. -Whatever you say, Mom.
മിറ റ്ലാധനാ ശ്ധല ഗ്വാ ടല], ന.
-What's happening? -We're getting thrown out, you idiot.
ഗ്വാ ൮9 ലാലിദ്വാ? 1 മിര്ഥ വിധ ല്ധധ, 0ഠഠ01..!
-You need a hand? -I got it.
ര്ധാലിധിരാമനധമ? ശ്വ 101൦൨ ധബടിത്ബത..
Here.
1൭൨..
So, you gonna miss me when I'm gone?
പഠി മഠ്മിയ്ബശ്ധ ലിത്ഥ നല്‌ ലിവ 0॥ മിവ ഠ്ദലാലഠ!?
-If l say no, do I still get your room? -Nope.
ദ്ര്ധ മിവ രര ലം, ഒറ മിവ മിര്ഥ ണമട। 0॥ലത്ധ?
Then, yes, I'll miss you.
ദ്രിമ്ധാല്റഡ, 3൭, മിവ മിവ ലനഠ്ധിത്ഥ ത്വ...
I can't breathe!
ചവ മലാംലവാലനല്മട!
-This can't be happening! -Quiet! What's that sound?
“ബി ല്ധാംി്സഡാലില്ഡ്‌ -21ബ! ഗാഥ ധാ
That's not trash. That's not trash!
1ധാധിത്ഥ ടബ്വാമ0.. ധവാധിത്ഥ ടമ്പാമ്വ
Think, think, Woody. Think, think, think.
1൨7, ഗദ 011൨...
Buster! Come here, boy! Come here!
ഒധട്‌ല ഗീ ടിബി, മല സീമ ടലി!
Okay, boy. To the curb!
8110൨, ബന. ലാ! ഭ ലാമി!
No, Buster! No!
110 3ധടല! ന്്ചിറ
-We're on the curb! -l knew it would come to this!
“രമാല ഠി ലവി മ്മ്‌ വ മധ 1ബ൭ മിരി വാലി!
Pull, everyone! Pull!
ചി ടലസ്ധാ ൦൧൮! ചിറ
-It won't rip! -Forget it!
ബര മിലാ -1ധ്രാമ്ദബമ!
It's triple-ply, high-density polyethylene!
1ബ൭ 001൮൭൦1൩ 3 ഘാന ര്‍ിഇ ഠി ബാ!
There's gotta be a way out!
[1111-11 1111
Andy doesn't want us. What's the point?
൧൨൦ ൭1 ലിറത്വഥ 102.. ൧3 റ്റാബ്‌?
Point. Point. Point!
ധ്യ, ഡ്വധാന, ധ്വര
Push! Push!
101 നംല്‌
I can hear the garbage truck!
ചവ ലാഠിലല്‍ി ഠ്ലറപ് ച ടമ്പാമ്വ
It's getting closer.
1൩൭ ദ ടണമിന്ന മ്വാമ്ധി
-Andy threw us out. -Like we were garbage.
ഠ്വ ലാധണാത്ഥ ന൭.. 5൦01൭൩൫1൦൭ ബി ടസ്വാല
-Junk. He called us junk. -How could he?
ടാബ്വാമ.. മ നണം! ൫൯൫ ടമ്മ.
This doesn't make any sense.
ബി ഖി നടധിം ലവി...
I should have seen this coming. It's Emily all over again.
ചവ ലാമധമ്ഡ ദ ലിദ്ഥാലിലിവ. 1൩൭ മ്പ ലാലി ടലയി। 9
-Sarge was right. -Yeah, and Woody was wrong.
-ഒല്‍ഡി ലിഷ്വാ ടമല]൩.. ട്ട റ്മ ഗ്‌ ട്വ
Wait a minute. Wait, hold on. This is no time to be hysterical.
ധാ ഠ്ധ്ധ്‌ ബാധിത നട ബമദഠി। ബ്ട്രലിരി
It's the perfect time to be hysterical.
ബ൭ ണനടടമ ൮൭ ടംടധലി ധഴിധുമഠി വടിവ്‌...
-Should we be hysterical? -No!
൧ദധധദ്ന്ല്വമഠി ബ്ടലിയി? റമി
-Yes! -Maybe! But not right now!
ട്‌ി പ്ള്‍്ധിന്ന..! നല്വാിലാധിത്ഥ ടലത്മാ!
Fellas, ! know what to do.
ദ്ധ മാ, മിവ ദ്വ്ഡ നല്ലാധമ! ലാമ...
What the heck?
൧3൮9 ലാലിമിവ?
-We should've done this years ago. -Jessie, wait. What about Woody?
[വമ ാദഡലാധാ ാല്റ്ബ്‌ ലാല ദ്ധ...
He's fine, Buzz. Andy's taking him to college.
1 031 ടല. ൧൨൦0 മീരാ ഠി 1൭ 1ില്.
Now we need to go!
ടിഗാ ന്മ ബട ലാലി!
You're right. Come on.
8ലഡി ലിയ്വാല.. ലോ
What's going on? Don't you know this box is being donated?
൧൮3൮9 ടര്‍്9ലാലില്വ്‌? നഠ്ലിദയ്സിമ്ധ 'ല്ധ ഗാലിബ്‌ ല്ര്ഥ ഠിലേന്നമ?
It's under control, Woody. We have a plan.
1]: 1112:111:1:1:111:1:11-111% [പ്ര ഠ്ദ ടമഡ മേല.
We're going to daycare!
[പ്ര ലിത്ഥ 1 ാധടമാല്വമാമ്ലബ്‌!
Daycare? What, have you all lost your marbles?
വടമ? ദ്ധ മാ ടലസ്ധട ൭0 9॥3 1൭?
Well, didn't you see? Andy threw us away.
ദ്ധ ഖില്ല? ൧൧൦ നല്പാധാറ 10..
No, no, no, no. He was putting you in the attic.
110൭1 ൧12 നല്ല്ല രസ്ധ ഠി ൦൦00..
Attic? So how did we end up on the curb?
പഠി വാഠറുമ്നമമ ാധിട ന്മ ാലമഠ്ദ റിലാ।ല്മ?
That was a mistake. Andy's mom thought you were trash.
1 ടമ ശടിപ്വാന.. നീലി ഥാ നിധ ത്സ്ഡ ബി ട്വാമ
Yeah. After he put us in a trash bag.
൮൭.. 1ലാദട ഠി നടി ന്മ 1 റിന്ന ാലു ടമബ്വാമ1..
And called us junk!
0 നലനാഠ॥ ൭ ട്വ
Yeah, I know. It looks bad. But, guys, you gotta believe me.
൭, മിവ ൭൨... 12 നമ ലിറ ചാ വ ണട്‌ രല മയേയിന്ഥ മിവ
Sure thing, college boy!
ടറി ഡ, ലാധ്ദ്ലേില!
Andy's moving on, Woody. It's time we did the same.
൧൧൦൮ നലല്ഡടിമന ബ്ധ്വോബയ, ഗ7൦ഠ൨..
Okay. Out of the box. Everyone, right now!
1ല്ധല ദ്വി രല. ടലസ്ഡാ 0൭, ടലദ്വാറവധമ!
Come on, Buzz. Give me a hand. We gotta get this thing outta here.
ഖമാ, ലാറി മിഡ്‌ [പമ ാലധ ദ്ല്യാിമബാലാഠ്യ ബി.
Woody, wait. We need to figure out what's best for everyone.
177000, ഡന്റ്‌! ൭ വാല നിഗിര്ഥ ഖാ 102൭1: ടലസ്ധമ ൦09
Great. Great! It's gonna take us forever to get back here.
ലാമ ൮൪൭ ത്ഥ ലബ്ബാ! നമടമ ഖമ ടലി ധി ഘാ! ദ ട്‌
It's all right, Barbie. You'll be okay.
12 ലാമ, ദദ്ലാട.. ദ്ധ ലിര്ഥ ലാലി ടല
Well, Molly and I have been growing apart for years.
ടലാലാബസ്ദ റീം ഠ്‌ മിവ ടലനലിന്ന [ലററ ടലിമണമ ാലാലമ്വാട മ്ഡറബി
It's just... 1 can't believe she would throw me away!
1൩൭ 0൫ബ൫൭.. ചവ ലിംാലമ്യേര 1:11: 111 1:111:1::111:11]
-Welcome to the club, toots. -Okay, everyone, listen up.
1 1111:11:-111] 1൭ ല്ലാ മ, ലാലലമ്പാധമറ..
We can get back to Andy's, but we gotta move fast.
[പമ ാഠില്‍ ഷമ്പാമി! 1൦ ലന്പാമ( ൧ 'ല്വാി ൭ നടടി ലാലല റിന്‌ ലോ
We'll hide under the seats till we get back home.
[പ്ര ലിത്ഥ ടല്ബാധസ്ഥ്‌ വോ ല്വാമ ഠ്ധ്ധി ടലവ്നാഠട ന൯ ധിമണാ
Get it through your vinyl noggin, Woody.
ലാല്ല പലി ട്ധമടടിനുര.. ൧൨0൨ ലിം ലിറമ്ലന്മ 199
He was putting you in the attic!
൧19 ഗല്ധ്ലല്റമ് ത്വ ഠിം!
He left us on the curb!
511:1[:1:1:11:111:111-11॥1:11:111
-All right, calm down! Both of you! -Okay, fine. Fine.
-831109൨, ലാലലാ! സ്ധലാലഠര്‍്ധല -3ലിന്ലി,ാലിഗമ്ല്‍
Just wait till you see what daycare’'s like.
ധാ ബ്നാമേദ്ധസ്ധ യ്ധാല്നേമമ മാധടമവാല്മാഠമ്ബഡ
-Why? What's it like? -Daycare is a sad, lonely place
1ലമ്വാമ? ദദറുല്നമ മഠ?
for washed-up old toys who have no owners.
ലനധിധവാലമാ നമ്മ ദ്ദ ലാസ!
-Quite the charmer, aren't ya? -You'll see.
111 111:1::11-1:1:11 1111൨ “ര്ധ മിഥ മ...
As soon as we get to daycare, you'll be begging to go home.
ടലാമ!॥ ടദ്യദ ന്മ ടമ്വാലി 1 ലാധടമാല്പമാമാഥ, വസ്ധ
Can anyone see anything?
8ഠിലി ൭ ടലടിലാദ 1൭ ലാദ-ലാമ?
-There's a playground! -Wow!
൧03 മനാബലാലന്നമ്നല്‌!
We hit the jackpot, Bullseye!
[പ്ര ദ്ദ്വാമ ധി ബഡി, ഒധിടലല്‍
So much for sad and lonely, huh?
5൦010൨ ദമ ടി ൮൭?
Okay. Calm down, guys. Let's just keep this in perspective.
8! ധാ 0൩൭ ബേധോലട്വാലയ്‌..
Perspective? This place is perfect.
ലെട്രാലവസ? ലമ്വാമ ബ്‌ ടല്വാധനട ടല.
Woody, it's nice! See? The door has a rainbow on it.
77000൮, 1൩൭ ലാട! 0൫൭൧൨ ൧൩൫൮ നലമ്പാഥബതയി ലാ! ഠി മട
-Hey there! -Wow!
ല്‍ വിടല്‍! ഗ്‌ഠഗി
Haven't seen you in ages.
ണമ മിധ്ധ്വാ വധ...
I just wanted to drop these old toys off.
ചവ ൩൭ മിലിര് ലമാ ന്ന ിനാ ബ്‌
Is this Bonnie? Look how big you are.
ബി ദം്ബ്ല ഒ? 1103ലാലയ്വാദലാടാബസ്മ !വവ..
-Say hi, sweetie. -Hi.
ലിയ്വാ വി, ടാ! 111.
Hey, how are your kids? Molly and Andy?
൧്വാ3 നല്ല ഥമലഗ്ഥല്ലത്ധ? നം ൦ ഡഥദ?
Not kids anymore. Andy's going to college on Friday.
8ധിരബാധഠ്ല്പാധഠ്ട്ലാ!.. ൧൧൦0 മിവ 1 രില്‌ ലി ധേന
-What? -Can you believe it?
്വാമ? ര്്ധാഠില്‍ ലാല മേമി?
-You sure they won't miss these? -No, they never get played with.
ദ്ധ വാടി നലലര ഖിദത്ഥ നല്‌ ബി?
-You see any kids? -Where is she taking us?
“ര്മധ ന്പവാല്ധാധഠ്ല്പാധ്ലേോ ലന 21 ലാമ 10൭ 1൪ നമ്മ?
What? What is it?
൧്വാ3 ബി?
What's the matter with you?
1ലദ്വാ ഠാ മഗ്യിര
I can't see!
ചവ മി്വാംല൨ ൯൧
Okay, everyone. Recess. Come on!
8110൨, ടലസ്ധദ ഥാ ടട ലിമ... ധ്‌
-So now what do we do? -We go back to Andy's.
ടല ലാമ! ഥല്ധാധാറ 1 ാധിമററ ൫ ബന ൧൨...
-Anyone see an exit? -Exit, shmexit. Let's get played with.
-ടലടിമ്യാമ മബ്വാലിധ്ുമി്മ ദ്ധ? 1ല്ധല, വ്വ ഡം നമ ലാലന്നമ്൩..
Careful. These toys might be jealous of new arrivals.
1120-02. ഗീലനഥ ബി നധററിന്ന ലേബ്ബാധധിത്ഥ ലഠ്ദമറ ലാമ
-I want to see! -Hey!
ചവ മില്മ
-Rex! -It's my turn!
1൩൭ 90 ലിയ
New toys!
ീല്നമബാലഡ്‌
Well, howdy! Glad to meet ya.
൧൮3 നല്ധാമഥ്‌ ലേബപാ।മധാലലസ്വ രധ..
Buzz Lightyear at your service.
ധമമ 1910 ൨ലലെ, ടലഠിദ നല്ബാബവ..
Boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
ചിന.
Thank you. May I?
ലിന 1൭ട10.. 801ല മിവ ടബ്‌?
The claw!
1ജിധലാലമലേോറ്റിഡിറ
Well, hello there. I thought I heard new voices.
ലിം ഠിടമമ..! ചവ ന ല്വ ലേല ടമാ
Welcome to Sunnyside, folks. I'm Lots-o'-Huggin’ Bear.
ടല ഠ്യ 1൭ ട്ടി, ദ്ധ 09! ചവ 1ഠ൦ടഠ 8ലധാഗാ ലനല്ധം
But please call me Lotso.
ചവ 01൦090 ലാഥാഠ॥ ലവ ട്ടം!
Buzz Lightyear. We come in...
8ധമമ 190൨ലെ, യബ്ി ദ്യ...
First thing you gotta know about me, I'm a hugger.
ലിവ ലാല്മണമ ദ്വ ാലിധ ഖ്ഡ വ മിവ,
Look at you all. You've been through a lot today, haven't ya?
110മിമ്നി്സ്വ ടലസ്ധമ. !(സ്ധ ദ്ദ നല്ദിധി ലാബിന്‌ ബി, ാധിര്ഥ?
It's been horrible.
1൩൭ ലിം.
Well, you're safe now. We're all castoffs here.
ദ്രസ്ധ ടല്ണമ ടല്ഷ്ഥമാ.. [പമ ടലസ്ധമ നല ഠ്ദാധനാ
We been dumped, donated, yard-saled, secondhanded
ബി ലച വാഡ, ഠി്ലേന്നമ, ദ്ധി ടേ സ്ധമ൨..
and just plain thrown out. But just you wait,
ലാമി ഠ്മഥ ഠി॥ധററധാല്റ്ഡ ടദ്വദ ച്വാ। മസ്ധ ഡാ ൦110.
you'll find being donated was the best thing that ever happened to ya.
ദ്രസ്ധ മിത്ഥ ധി ൮൭ നല ന്ന ദ്ലന്നമ..
Mr. Lotso, do toys here get played with every day?
50. ॥ഠ1ടഠ? ൧0൭1൨ നമ്മ വിട്ബി റിന്ന ടലില്വാ ല്ലി?
All day long. Five days a week.
ടലാമബ്[നാ ൫. 5 ൪ ടലമ്്നാഠധ
But what happens when the kids grow up?
൧3൮9 ലാലിമലിവ 0॥മാധഠ്ദ്ലാധഠ്ല്ലുദഠിലാടടമല?
Well, now, I'll tell ya.
ദില മിവാലിയ്ഡിത്വ.
When the kids get old, - hew ones come In.
8॥ ാധഠ്മ്പാധഠ്മ്ലാടടമല, ൮9 വാമ ലിന ണമടധ
When they get old, new ones replace them.
8112 ബ്0ിധ്ദഠി! ഡാ, ൮൭ വാഡ ല്ദ്ഥ നല ്സിര്ഥ ബ്0ിം.
You'll never be outgrown or neglected, never abandoned or forgotten.
ദ്ധ യിറരബ്ദഠി ലിദ്ധ 1൭൦ മ്ധ ഠി ലാലി.
No owners means no heartbreak.
॥॥- 1-11-11: നമി 90൭ ടലഠി0ഥ
-It's a miracle. -And you wanted us to stay at Andy's.
1ബ൭ ടമഡ ശല്വദ്ധാമന..
Because we're Andy's toys!
ടലാലാ ന ബി നമല്നഥ ൧
So you got donated by this Andy, huh?
പഠി ദ്വ ഠിഠ്ലന്നാ ൦ല൨ ൧൧൨7
Well, it's his loss, Sheriff. He can't hurt you no more.
ബ൭ വിമ ഠിം, ടല 11:11 11111]: 111 11:11]
-Whoa, whoa, no, no, no... -Now, let's get you all settled in.
എഡി. 1മാധമ്ിര്ഥ ദ്വസ്ധ ടലീടടമ
Ken? Where is that boy? Ken? New toys!
(൭൦൩? സീമാധഠ്ല്ലഡയ? 11:11:
Far out! Down in a jiff, Lotso.
ലാമ സ്ഥ ില്ലാ മാ, ॥.ഠട൦..
So, who's ready for Ken's dream tour?
പഠി, ടില്വാ ൮9 ലാലടലഠിദ ധിധമധമ്ഥ സ്ലിമ ന?
Let's show our new friends where they'll be staying.
എഡി ഡബ്ധി്ഥേ മഡ്ഥിയധമലാഥഡ ന്മ
Folks, if you want to step right this way...
ദ്ധ മാ, രിദ്ധിദ്ധ വല്ലി...
Hi, I'm Ken.
11, മിവ 4൭൨൩..
Barbie. Have we ever met?
ലാം. 0൭ ലാനണമ്പാലലസ്വ ദ?
I would've remembered.
0-ധ, മിവ ഗഡ 093...
-Love your legwarmers. -Nice ascot.
-ടധിയിത്ഥ ടഠിന്നാ രദ ധ്ധ.. ഗാലി മടിരലിര്ധ
Come on, Ken. Recess don't last forever.
ലാമ 4ല൨.. ീടടമ ലിമലാധ്ത്ഥ നടു ിലനാ
Right on, Lotso. This way, everybody.
810, 1൦൭൦! ൧൭൨ ബി, ടലസ്ഡാ ൦009..!
You got a lot to look forward to, folks. The little ones love new toys.
ദ്ധ ൦09 ലിന നലസ്വാധസമി ന൭ട൭ ൮9 ലാമ...
-What a nice bear. -And he smells like strawberries.
-ഒലഡധമനാ 9 വാലി. ബാധ ഠി ടലാലി ടന്മ്ഥാലി
Folks, if l can share, here at Sunnyside, we've got,
ദ്രിദ്ധ മിവ ാംില്ഡാലിശറടി, ഠി ടധ്സ്ട്രി്ടേ..
well, just about anything a toy could ask for.
09 നലമ്പാധബയി ല്വാദ ടദ്വദ ൮9 ലാലാ നമ്നഥ ഗബ്ത്ഥ
Spare parts, superglue,
ചീറ്റി റി, ലാലില്‍ വമ...
and enough fresh batteries to choke a Hungry Hungry Hippo.
00 1ാ൭ലി ൮ ഗോഡ്വാ ധി നലംല്വം്വാം ൮9 ടാമി്ലാല
-Think you're gettin’ old? -Wow.
ദ്ര്ധ നിന്നലിര്ധ ചേ ഡമ്‌?
Well, stop your worryin’.
പ്ല ലിടദ്ധ..!
Our repair spa will keep you stuffed, puffed, and lightly buffed.
ട്രാമാല്പാലിത്ഥ ന്മ ദിത്ഥാമടി്ഥ ന്ധ ലാലമഠ്ട ഠിന ഭാമ ാറവട
And this, well, this is where I live.
മഥ ഠിട്ബില മിവ നാ...
It's Ken's Dream House. It has a disco, it's got a dune buggy.
ബ൭ ധന ്വാിമ ൭൨.. 1 നലമ്പാഥബയി ഠ്ടിധ,
And a whole room just for trying on clothes.
ഉമ്ഥ ടമ ॥॥॥॥ലാടടദ്ധ ധി നലധോമ ല്വ്
You have everything!
ദ്ധ നലമ്വാധബയി ടമ്മി!
Everything except someone to share it with.
ടല്റമിദ-റുമ1മ൩൭.. ധി ൦09 ധി൦ണലഘാരനാടിര്സുര
You need anything at all, you just come talk to me. Here we are.
ദ്രിമ്ധ ന്ധ ലാലിധിത്ഥ ല്ാമ-ല്വാമ, ദ്വ ഠ്ദ്മാ1മ്ഡാല്ധ്പാദ ലിവ.. ബി ദില
Well, thank you, Big Baby.
ലിന 1൭50, 819 8ഖ..
Why don't you come meet our new friends?
൧3 ൪൭ ദ്വ ദ്ദ വ്ധ്പാമ മഡ്ഥിയധമലാഥഡ ന്മ
Poor baby. We were thrown out together, me and him.
ലട ടി ാമ0.. (ബി ദ്വാധമനാ ാലടമനാ, മിവ ഠ്മ ഠി1ഒ..
Abandoned by the same owner.
ഗാലി ത്ബാലമി॥വു ട്നട..
But we don't need owners at Sunnyside.
ചവ ൭ ലിാലിധിത്വാലസി॥॥ ഠി ടധ്സ്ട്രി്ടേ..
We own ourselves. We're masters of our own fate.
പമ നല ഠി ന്൯ ടലി... വമ ബി ഡാഥ ലിര്ലാന്മ.
We control our own destiny.
[പമ നല്ലി പര്ധാന ടലഠ്ല്‌
Watch out for puddles.
1120-00 ബധലത്ഥ മ...
And here's where you folks'Il be stayin’.
മഥ ഠിട്ബിമ്ത്ധ 0 ലിദ്ഥ ണാ...
The Caterpillar Room.
81॥॥ധിമലിഥ്ഥടേട!
-Look at this place. -Wow!
1101൭0 ല്പാമബ..
Holy moly guacamole.
ചിന
Jackpot, baby.
ഉറി ഡയ, ടമയ൭ന൭..
-Whoa, puppy! -Hello.
0൦0൭, മമ മബ്നാ!
It's so beautiful!
ബ൭ ടാ ദേണ്ദിറ
What the... Hey, little guy.
ലി, മഡ്മറ 1൭൦॥..
How long's it been since you all got played with?
ഉമ്പാലമ്വാദ ണന ടല സ്വ ഠിനല്ബ്ത്ന?
It's been years.
ഉ്ഡാലന്മ്ധന ണമ.
Well, just you wait. In a few minutes, that bell's gonna ring,
ധന ടല്വദ.. ഠി ാലാലയ്വാട ബ്ബ 1ഠലേഡോ മിരബാബാധസി..
and you'll get the playtime that you've been dreamin’ of.
2 -111:11111:1:111111:111:1111-11] ൮ സ്വ ലിമ്പന്ധിത്ഥ
Play! Real play! I can't wait!
ഗീച്ബ്‌ നില്‌ ടലാലല! ചവ ലം ടപാല്‌
Now, if you'll excuse us, we best be headin’ back.
മിമധ ദ്ധ വ്ധ്ട, നഅ൯ നടട 0൦.
Welcome to Sunnyside, folks.
ടല മ്മാ ഭട്ടി, ദ്ധ ൦00൭..
-Thank you. -Take care, pinky.
ലിന 1൭511.
-Goodbye, Mr. Lotso. Thank you. -Thank you, buddy boy.
-ടലണമ 009, 5൨. ടം! ലിന ൭ട॥൩..
-Will l see you again? -I'll see you tonight
൧0൭1൭൫ മിവ ലിര്ബാല്വധമ്പാ ന്ധ 1? വ മിരബ്ധ്വാ ദ്ധ നമിമന ബി.
in my dreams.
ിനമ്പ്സ്വാ മിവ
Ken, let's get a move on.
110൭1. 1൭൩, മയി ന്മ ലാലഠ!..
Barbie, come with me. Live in my dream house.
ഡി മിവ.. ന വ്ബനമ്പന്ധ്മന മിവ..
I know it's crazy. I know we just met.
ചവ മധ ൩൫൭ 919.. ചവ മ്ഡ ന്മാ ട്വ ലാനലസ്ധ.
Heck, you don't know me from G.I. Joe,
ദ്ധ മിധാലയ്വാദ ൨൭ മിവ
but when I look at you, I feel like we were...
'ല്വാ ദ മിവ നലമലര്ധ.. മിവ ടമ ടലാലി 0൭ ബി...
-Made for each other. -...made for each other.
-20മട॥॥ഥ ധം ടമഡ ടന ലന. -20മട॥മഥ ധിം ടാഡ ടന്ന?
-Yay! -Yes.
൭...
-Ken? -Coming, Lotso.
രര? വ ദ്ദ ബി, ട്ടം
This is so exciting!
ബി ടാ നലാധ്ല്ത്ല്‍
Sounds like kids to me.
ഒധബ്ിബ൭ നമടമേന ദ്വല്ധിത്ഥലം ാഠ്മ മിവ
I want to get played with. Why can't time go faster?
ചവ മിറിനമ്ബ്ത്ഥ. ലദ്വാാണമടമ 'ലിധാംില്ഡാലില്ധ ബിലാ ലോറ
How many you reckon are out there?
ദ്ധ ടമ ലാല്വാദ ണമി ൮9 309 ദ്ധ ടമ്മ?
They sound so sweet.
ീബ്ടമ പാഥ്‌ നലല
Look, everyone, it's nice here, I admit.
ഉല്ല, ടലസ്ധമ ൦09, ബാലി ഠിടില്‍ി, മിവ മിഡി.
But we need to go home.
ചാ ന്ധ മട ലാധ്ഥാ
We can have a whole new life here, Woody.
1പമാഠിലി ബി॥॥നഭ്ബ്ധോമ്ഥ ൮9 വാമ ഠിട്ബി, ഗ്‌ഠഠഠ
A chance to make kids happy again.
ഉല്ധാററ ധിധാധമ്ധിര്ഥ വ്വല്പര്ഥല്റലമ്പാന്ഭ ടലി! ൭9!
-Why don't you stay? -Yeah, Woody. Stay with us.
1111111111 ട്‌ ഗ്‌. ന൩നലില ബിര
-Come on, Woodster! -You'll get played with.
എഡി, ഗ൦ംംഠ്ട്ല്‌
-I can't. No. -Stay here.
ചവ മിധവാംല൨
-You can make a new kid happy. -No, no. Guys, really. No!
100 വിടല്‍. ധി ത്ഥപ്്ലത്ഥല്വാ ലാല ലേബാ।ഭ.
I have a kid. You have a kid. Andy!
ചവ നലമ്പാധബതയി ടലം09 ഠി. ദ്ധ നലമ്വാധബയതി ടലം09 വാധഠ്ലിം ൧൧൦
And if he wants us at college, or in the attic,
ഉറ വ്ി്ധ ദി നാ്ബ്ത്ിന്മ ശല... ഒ 0൦൭,
well, then, our job is to be there for him.
ഡാമട ൯ മില ധിധാനെറ്ട ദിടാമ ധി
Now, I'm going home.
ചവ ലിലാധിമാ
Anyone who wants to join me is welcome. Come on, Buzz.
ടടടില്വാ ൮ നമ്ലിവഡ ലിവ ദില്ധ്ത്ഥ. എഡി, ധമ്മ
Our mission with Andy is complete, Woody.
്പ്ടി। ന ൦ ൧൧൦ ലി ടല്ടടലി
What?
൧്പാമ?
And what's important now is we stay together.
൧3൮9 ലാറാ ലിന ണടടിി നാലി ലാലടാണമ
We wouldn't even be together if it weren't for Andy!
[പ്ര ്ിശബാലടമനാ ്ിധാധിത്ഥ ത്ഥ ഥ്‌
Look under your boot, Buzz. You, too, Jessie.
1102 വവാമഡമാധ്ധര്ധ, ധമ്മ ദ്ധ, ൭ലടടില.
Whose name is written there?
പണട ടില്വാ ൮9 ലധിട വാമി ടമ?
Maybe Andy doesn't care about us anymore.
്ധനാ।ന്ന ൧ ജിധ്ടേല 1111411115]
Of course he does. He cares about all of you!
ടറി ഥഡ ഠി 1ര്‍്ടല. ഉ മമ്പാ॥ ലമ മററ സ്ധ ടലസ്ധല
He was putting you in the attic. I saw.
൧1 നല്ല്ല രസ്ധ 61൦09. ചവ മമ്വാമിം.
You can't just turn your back on him now!
്രസ്ധ മലാല നാഠലിത്ഥ ഠിദ ടലര്മമാ!
Woody, wake up! It's over! Andy is all grown up!
177000, ടലി! 1൩൮൭ 51 മന ൧൨0൨ റമ ലാടടല!
Okay, fine. Perfect.
80, ാലിധ്്ലാമ;
I can't believe how selfish you all are.
ചവ മലാല ാലദ്വാ യസ്ധ ാല്ന്ിത്ഥ ൦
So this is it? After all we've been through.
പഠി, ബി ടദ്യദ? 1ലാമട ടലറ്റമിമബ 9 10൭ ൫൧0൦
Bullseye, no. You need to stay.
ഒധിടലുട, 0൭ ദ്ധ ലട ണാ! വ്ട്ബ
Bullseye, no, I said, "Stay!"
ഒധിടലട. നലം ലിവ മര, "ന്നാല്‌"
Look,
ലാല,
I don't want you left alone in the attic, okay? Now, stay.
ഒിവ ഖി൦ഥല്ലത്ധലാലടലറഠിന്മ ലു, ല്മണ? ടല, ന്മ
I gotta go.
ചവ മട ലാല!
Bonnie, you in here?
8ംഹബ്ല, ദ്ധ ഠിനട്ബി?
Come on. Come on. Oh, no, no.
കൃഡധി. ഡീ. ൦൨9
What... What the heck?
൧്വാ ലിബ്ര?
Now, that's better.
ട്ല്യ്മാ, വ ലാ്പാലി
There you are. Come on, honey. It's time to go home.
1ധാധല ത്വ. ഷഡി, ടമ. ഉ ധാമ നടടബമ ധിധാധി്ദാ
No, no, no, no!
൨൦ ിഠ്ച്റ
Reach for the sky!
൦ ഒ്വാക്്‌'ക7 !ദഗവ്‌
You're my favorite deputy.
€ദഥ്‌ദ7 ൧2ലാഠ070 7റെലനക7ഥ ദ്ധ
-Bonnie! -Coming!
ചവ ഠിമ്മ്ഥറുബി!
Great.
൨0൨ 0ലാ%
It's gonna be okay, Bullseye.
1൩൭ മരാം ഒധിടലുട
Woody's going to college with Andy. It's what he's always wanted.
177000 മിറ ൭ ശില ദ ൧0൦. ധാ വട ടലില്ധ നബ്ത്ഥ
He's crazy. College is no place for a toy.
ഠി 9॥3. 14ഠില്‍ വാധ്വ ല്വാമ ധിം ണല്നമ്ന
Toys are for playtime.
ഗീഥ ലിമ ധം നട ലാല്നമ്ന
Speaking of playtime, they're lining up out there!
മിശ്വാലാമടമി നാട ലാലനനമ്ന, നലല ടലഠ്ദററ ലാലയഡ വിധ ടല!
-How many? -There must be dozens.
-ഒലഘ്വാമ മനി? ടി ലഡ ാലാലദഘ്വാമ ഠ്ഠമല
I can hardly wait!
ചവ ൭ ടലാമറ്‌
Places, everyone!
൧മ്പാ॥ ലമ്പാമ ടലസ്ധദ ൦09
At last! I'm gonna get played with!
ചന്ത! ലിവ ലദ്ഥ ഠിനല്ബ്തബല്‍്‌
-Rex? -Come to papa.
ലു 2) 1::1:11:111::1:1:1-1
There's a snake in my boot.
൧ീറ്ദ ല്‌ദ്൦ ന്നാ ൧൧ ൮
I'd like to join your posse, boys, but first I'm gonna sing a little song.
ചവ ഥന ടക്‌ ൧ധ്വാഥ്കഗ :൭ഥാല 43൧ 070
A sheriff!
ടല ടല!
Move over, Mr. Pricklepants.
8ലിത്ഥ ഡമാ, 5൨.൧ഥലിംലോദബ്ട.
We have a guest. You want some coffee?
[പ ഠി ല്മസ്ധ ദ്ധ ലില്ലി?
It's good for you. But don't drink too much, or you'll have to...
ബര ലാദടട ധിലമത്വ. ന്യ സ്സ ബി ടനാഠംമ്ത്ധ ദ്ധ നമി
Be right back!
ലലാമിടമ-- ചവ ലിദ്ഥ ഘമ്പാമ! ഷ്ല്വാ1॥!
Hey, hello? Hi. Excuse me.
റല ലം? 11 നീലിര്ഥ ലിവ
Can you tell me where I am?
8ഠിലീദ്ധലാലിമ്ഡ ദിവ ദിനാ ലിവ ാലയഠ്മ? ടവ
The guy's just asking a question.
ല്ലി ഡ ബ൭ ൩൭ ടമ ടംലിമ്ഥ
Well, excuse me. I'm trying to stay in character.
ീമലിദ്ഥ മിവ. ചവ ൩൭ ധോമദ്ലിബത്ഥ ധാടെ ലിവ
My name's Buttercup. You've met Baron von Shush.
പണട മിവ 8ധലധ്വ. ദ്ധ ്്പ്യധസ്വാഠ 8൦൩൦൦0 ട്ട
Hello, I'm Trixie.
പ്ലം, മിവ ന്ലാറംല
Guys, hey. Guys, look, I don't know where I am.
ദ്ധ ൦09, ഠിബാല, മിവ ഖമ്ഡ നാഥ മിവലാലമഠ്മ
We're either in a café in Paris or a coffee shop in New Jersey.
[പര ടനാഠ്ദലാലമഠ്ദ റി ദ്വ ഠി ദ്്ട ഒ 1൪ 1:൧0 ഠി ലഗ്‌ പലടലു
I'm pretty sure ] just came back from the doctor
ചവ ാമടി മിവ ലാമ ട്വമ !ഭമ്പാലി! ദ്മ്0ി ഠഠറ൧൦
with life-changing news.
ദാലി മിത്ഥ നലാറധാമബിഠ്വോ ലിവ
We do a lot of improv here. Just stay loose, have fun, you'll be fine.
1പമാബയ്ലാലില്ഥ ദിട്ബ്‌. ലില്പാലടലഠാപമ്ധ മ്രാല ട്വ
-No, no, no, no. I... -Who wants lunch?
1:1:1:111:-11111:15:11111:1:111:1110
It has a secret ingredient. Jelly beans.
1 നല്പാഥബയി ലാല ബഖീടിമ. ലാന
Somebody's poisoned the water hole.
൧09 070 )9 ?ല്ക7 ഗുലദഗ്ഥല്‌ ഗാദ!ദ ക7്‌
Poison? Who would do such a mean thing?
മാഡ്‌? ടല്വാ 39 മിരബാധമ ടംടധമവ ട്രാധധ?
The scary witch! Look out! She's using her witch-y powers!
ഗ7ബ്ര ട്വ നല്ല്ഡത്ബ്‌ ൨9010 1 നലഥാാധ്നല്ത്ഥ വടട ടിയ!
“I Know where to hide."
ചവ പ്ഡ നമ ലം ടലമ്പാഥസി
She'll never find us in here.
ഉ ലിറബ്ധന്പാ ന്ന ഠിട്ബ
What's wrong?
൧്വാ ലിബ്ര?
She found us! We need a spaceship to get away from the witch!
൧19 ലിമ്പ്ധ്വാല ന്ധ [പമ ാലിധിത് സ്വാമി ബാരടദ ധ0%
-You're doing great! -Are you classically-trained?
“ര്മധ ല്വിത്ഥ ൦ ലാമ ടലി! “ര്മധ 0112൧0 ടേ ദ്മടിധി?
Look, I just need to know how to get out of here!
ചവ മബ൩൫൭ ലാല മധ ാററമ്നമമ ലല്ലശ്ധല ദ്ദ ടബ്‌!
There is no way out.
ലിറ്റി ല്ധല
Just kidding. Door's right over there.
11ബമ ലാല. ൧൩൮ ഠഠ്ഒ വ്ടലാലമ൩ ടമ്മ
Well, cowboy, you just jumped right in, didn't ya? I'm Dolly.
ഠാ, ദ്ധ 2൭ ന്ധി ഠ്ണണ ടലാലമ, ധി? ഷ്വ ഉം.
Really? You're gonna stick with that?
ഒലധിയി്? ദ്ധ ലിം ട്സ്പാന ഗണ ധ്‌?
‘Cause now's your chance to change it, new room and all.
ടലാലാ ടല ലാല്ധമ ദ്വ ധിം നല്ലാ,
That's coming from a doll named Dolly.
1 റിമ ദി ാമധനാ ദ ലാണമനട ൦1
-Who's the new guy? -Are you a real cowboy?
-ടല്വാ ല്ലാ ധ? “1ര്ധ യാ ടലാലല് ൭?
-Well, actually... -'Course he's not, pea brain.
-ടലാലമ യത ടലി ഹല ിഠ്മ്ലലാഠഠ്ഠ
-He don't even have a hat. -I do too have... My hat!
212 ദമ ണലസ്പാധബയയി 1൧01 ലാധന. വ റ 101--7001 മയ!
-Told ya. -l found a spaceship!
“ര മിവാലിമ്ഡത്ധ. വ ദ്ദ്വ്യധമ്പാമ ന്വാഠമി ിരടല
Showtime.
സീമടടമ പാലി
Quick, get in. Fasten your seat belts.
ലാ, നടടധിറമ. 05 ൭! ശിലഠ്ല.
Close your tray tables. Hold on. It might get a little bumpy.
ടസ്വാഥ നല നലിത്ഥ ലററ ധാ 1൩൭ സ്ധാിന്ന ലഡിം
Three, two, one, blastoff!
3,2, ലാലിയ
You saved us, cowboy. You're our hero.
ലഗ്‌ [ദ്ധ ലി൭0 ടല്ചനമിര്ഥ മി, യാം. (ധി ഡ്‌ യ്‌
I got a kink in my slink.
൧്ിവ റ ലേല
My tail! Where's my tail?
ലല മിഡ്‌ സീദ ല്ധ മിവ?
Someone need a hand?
൧0൭ 009 ലാലിധിര്ാബവഡമ?
-Where's my nose? -Here it is.
1:11: ബി ഠി
-Here's your arm. -Give me that. That's mine.
ബി ഠി മഥമ്ത്ധ.
Honey, the mustache?
ടാറു, നമ സബ്്ടപ്ബത?
I don't recall playtime being quite that strenuous.
ചവ മിലാ നാമ നട ലാലന്ന 11111111
Andy never played with us like that.
൧൧൦0 മലാല നല്ന ്ബോന്മാലറിഡ
We're just gonna have to make the best of it.
[പ്രമ ണടട॥ി ധോ ധബടിമബമ
But these toddlers, they don't know how to play with us.
ചാ മറലിപത്ഥല്ലബി, നലല മമ്ഡ ാറ്റമ്നാഥമ ലിം ണമ ബിന
-They're too young! -Yeah, they're sticky.
പ്ീലലയ ലില്ധ സ്ധഠ്ല! അ, നലല്ര നലല
Well, we should be in the Butterfly Room.
[പ്ര മഡടാലമഠ്ട ഠി 0॥॥മനമ-മനാ
-With the big kids! -That's right.
എറ്റ്ാധഠര്‍്ലിറയരാടടമ്‌ ലഡഡ
-Yeah, you said it. -We'll get this straightened out.
വ ടലഡ്വധ. വ മിഥ ധബടിര്ബ്ബുര
I'll go talk to Lotso about moving us to the other room.
ചവ ലിത്ഥ ദേമശ്വാ 0 ॥ഠടം ടധ്യാമു൭ ാ0റിമ്വ്ത്ഥിസ്മ ലാ ിമ്ന
Blast. Try that one.
ചി്ദനലം. ധോ ഡയ
It's locked!
1൩൭ റിഡ്!
-Same here. -Try the windows.
ടന ട്രാബി ധാമ റിവാ
Negatory. It's a Fenster-Schneckler 380.
1മിധാഠിലല്‍. 1൩൭ ൦ട്ല-ടന്ലടറല
Finest childproof lock in the world.
ഗീ യിട ദ്ഥല്ലത്ഥലം ൮9 0210 ലാട ഠിദ്ധബ്മ
-We're trapped! -Wait.
ര ല്ലാല്ഥായയാ! “ററ
Did anyone notice the transom?
൧03 ൭1 ടടടില്വാദ ലട നായാ ഭം?
Oh, great. How do we get up there?
൨0 ലാമ. ദാഠല്നാഥട നമ ഠി മലിലഭ മട ടമ?
All right, everyone. On three! One, two...
8110൨, ടലസ്ധദ ൦09. ാമഠ്ദന്തമമഥ 9 ടമഡ..ഠ്ധ2...
Let go!
1ലാദടിയബത!
Go!
1ഠമ്പാമ്‌
-He did it! -Yes, sir!
21 ലി] മിഡി! ട്ട ഡ്മ
Way to go, Buzz!
ട്രൃയ്വാമട, 822
Yeah, you think they had a fun playtime?
ദ്ധ 70 നലല ടലഠ1ധാലനല്ന?
They might hear you.
51. ഗീലല്ര സ്ഥാന ലോല ത്ധ
-Okay, now you start. -l...
-ടലവ്വയാററ ദ്ധ സ്ധിലിത്ഥ ്വ൨..
-Love... -You.
യ്ത... ചിര!
See? That time, I said "love." Okay, now me first.
ബ്‌ 0൫൭൧൨ നീടടമഡ ലിവ രമ "ബേത്‌. ട്ല്ദ്ധമാ മിവ ്ധ്ധ.
-Okay, okay, okay. -l...
-83110ിലീ വവ...
-Love... -You.
യ്ത... രവ.
You see what I mean? It changes every time.
ര്ര്ധ ന്പാലിന 1ബ൭ലാലഡിാമറ ടലില്വാ യി
You are so smart.
്ര്ധ ടാ ലാല്‍
Come on, Romeo. We're late.
1110111111):
-I'll wait up for you. -Kisses!
വ മിരത്ഥ ഡേ ധിംത്ധ ്ധനാബ!
All right, place your bets. Come on, everybody.
ധി ലാലാ, മയാ. 1:11: 1
-Come on. Any splits? -Heya. Bring it here.
ശൃഡി, ടലസ്ധ ൦09. ഠി ാമ്ഠാറിന? ബിദിദ
-Come on, horsey, come on! -Come on, turkey, come on, turkey.
ശൃഡം വര്‍ദ, മധ ഛശൃഡി, മുത ലാല.
-Gobble, gobble, baby. -Come on, horsey.
പ്റില്്ഥ, നിത, ടമ്മ. ഒദഡയിത്ഥ ദ്ധി ധിം ലിവ
Come on, duck.
കുഡയിവ്യ ദ്ദ.
-All right, that's it. No more bets. -Come on! Right here.
“1109 19 ലാല്ല ഛശൃഡിം, മയ! കയ്‌ ഉട്ബി!
Let me have the duck, let me have the duck, let me have the duck!
ദില മിവ റ്ഖ്വാദ്ധിദ്ഥ റ
Here is a duck.
ബി 1൭0
-l won! -Ah, man!
ചവ റമ നല്‌!
-Well, Stretch takes the round. -You lost!
50൦0൩ നമാ ടന ബി. “ര്മധ മിമ്വ
Okay, minimum bet, five Monopoly.
ലീ ബ്ബ്നമ: [നദ ീംലാം॥.
-Coyote's wild. -Here, here.
6൮0൭൦ 11
-Two greens here. -Changing two double A's.
ഥമ ്[് ഠിട്ബി. പ്രീല്ധിശ്വ ഠ്ധ ഥവാലനഠ്ദ
Hey, what do you guys think of the new recruits? Any keepers?
൧3 ലാലഠ്ലാദ ദ്ധ മഥ 1ലിന്ധ്ധാമഡ?
Oh, please! Landfill!
1111141111:
-Cowgirl? Dinosaur? -Toddler fodder.
10100 ഉലഘലമ്പാധഥ? ൧നംടമ്ധല? പ്രില്ദാഥദ്ഥല്പത്ഥലിം
But that space guy, he could be useful.
ദാഠല്നാനാ ബില്ലറി മബാ1യടമ? 01 സ്ധഥനാ്സാലാഥനമ
He ain't the sharpest knife in the place where they keep the knives.
ഉ ാധിത്ബാധമ ടാ... ലസ്വാമ റിനമ ണലല്ഠര ടസ്വാഥ ല്ടദ്ധ
Neither are you, Chunk.
ലഗാ ഠി ബദ്ധ, ന്ധ
You got a little keeper yourself, didn't you, Ken?
ദ്ധ ്ല്വാമ॥ ടലടധമഡ ധ0റിടസ്വാന,ലാധിത്ന?
Hey, lay off, Twitch. Barbie's different.
പറ്്ിരാദ്ധേ മവ, സ്ഥ്ധീ ലാല മ൩.
Aw, Mr. Softy over here.
൧ 50. 1ലമ്പാധ്‌ വ്ട്ബി
What do you expect from a girl's toy?
൧3൮9 വ നമ ദ്മലി നമ്നാബാധദ്ല്ധാലലമ്പാധമ?
I'm not a girl's toy! I'm not! Why do you guys keep saying that?
ചിവാധിദ്ഥ നമല്നമബാധഠര്‍്ലിാലലസ്പാധമബല്‍്‌ ചി്വലാധ്തല്‍്‌
All them toys are disposable.
ടലസ്ഡാ നമ്മ ധാംലല്‍ി വിധ
We'll be lucky if they last us a week.
[പമ ലിര്ബാലനണമട॥ വാലി മധ നലല ലാലല ടബ്‌
Well, well. Looky who we have here.
110 മിമ ടില്വാ മഠ്ദ ഠിട്ബ
Let me go!
1ലാദടിയ്ഥ മഡ്‌
Take him to the libary.
ദാ ഠി 1൭ രല്ാധട്മിരമ്ഥ
Woody, what are you doing?
77000, ലാ ൮9 വ ാധാറ
I gotta get outta here.
ചവ നടടി ഘ്ധല്॥ മലി ടബ്‌.
-You're leaving? -But didn't you have fun today?
“രമ നലിലാലയ॥? “ദ്വ ൨ ഖി ടല ലി ബി?
Well, of course I did, more than I've had in years,
ടലഠിമ ഗഡ മിവ ടല 1ലാ। ഠി ലാല്യ്ഡ നബ
but, you see, I belong to someone else.
'ല്വാ। ല്വ സി॥॥ഗ 1൭0
-Who's "Yid-nuh"? -Il believe it's pronounced "Yid-nay."
ട്രല്വാദ നിപ? എവ ടാ ബ൭ ഠിടലാധ്‌ നിമ
Guys, it says "Andy."
ദ്ധ 0൦09, 1൩൭ ൧൧൨
He's my Bonnie.
ഉ 8ംബ്ല മിവ,
And he's leaving soon. I gotta get home.
ദമ റിമ മിഥ ാലയ। ഖ്ധ്ലനാ 1൭1. ചവ ണനടട॥ി രാധാ
-Where's home? -Elm Street. 234 Elm.
പഥി നമ ര്ധ? മി ടന. 234 ചി ടീന.
-You guys have a map? -We're on it, cowboy. Trixie?
ിര്ധ മറി ലാമ? ചവ്ര്മ മിത്ഥ ലാല ന്ധ, വാം
I'll fire up the computer.
ചവ ലിര്ഥ സ്ധില്ദ്ഥിരമ്പാധ്ല
Unhand me, you cowards! I demand to talk to Lotso!
1ലാദടിയ്ഥ മിവ, ലബ്‌ രണ്ധ! വ മിലാലലിത്വാ 9൩ 1ഠടം!
Zip it, Buck Rogers.
ബില, ഒല മംലട.
You don't talk to Lotso till we say you can...
രവ യിധാംില ലേന്വാ 60 ഠടം ടലവ്നാഠട ൯ ൭൪ ത്വ ാഠ01ല൨--
Ken? What's goin’ on here? Why is this toy tied up?
(ലാ? ഥാ ലാലില്വ വ്ട്ബി? 1ലമ്വാ നമാ ബി വ॥൭൧ാ
He got out, Lotso.
1൭ ല്ലാടടിദറ ഠി, ॥ഠ1ട൦
“Got out"? No, no, no, no, no. This isn't how we treat our guests.
1ലാമടിയ്ഥ ഠ്ല? ൨൨ 9ദ്ചഴിഠ്ലി
F-A-Oh, my Schwarz. There you go. I'm so sorry.
6-2 0൨, മിണ 1ധ റിദ. ഗീലിമര്ഥ ലിവ
-Lotso, there's been a mistake. -A mistake?
1015൦, മഠ ടവ !ടില്യാമഥ. ഒട ല്ാമഥ?
The children in the Caterpillar Room are not age-appropriate
ദ്രമ്ലത്ഥല്റഥിന 8॥॥ധിമമല്ധ്ടേട... 1 ടടടധല ധസ്ധ്ര
for me and my friends.
1:11: 1:11 1111]
We respectfully request a transfer to the Butterfly Room.
ബി ഠി നന്നമന്ര നല്്നമ നല്ലാ മനാമ
Well, request granted!
ലമ്പ്ന്മാഥ റിയലി
-But, Lotso... -Hush now, Kenneth.
“1 ല്വാ। ഠട൦.. -൧1ണ ബന
This toy's shown initiative, leadership.
നിച്നഥ ബ്‌ നല്ഡബ്ധിദ്ത്ഥേ ബിടി, ഘാ।്പനമ്
Why, I'd say we've found ourselves a keeper.
ചവ ലിര്ഥ രര ഗ്ര റ്ഖ്വപ്യധ്വാടാ നമ്നഥ ധിറിട്സ്വാല
Hear that, everyone? We got a keeper!
ലാല ഡ, ടന്ഡാ 0? 1 ::1-1:1:111-1111:111- 11:11
We're calling you up to the big leagues, son.
ബി നമിധ്യല്പാധ്ധമ്ധ 1ഭ 19 ാടടല, [1]. :
From now on, you'll have anything you want.
ീധിമ! ടല, ദ്ധ മിത്ഥ ്ല്ാദ്ധിദ്ഥ വാദ ട്വ വയ്വ ലിം
Excellent. I'll go get my friends.
ലാമ. ഷിവ മിത്ഥ ലാല! ഠ്ല്രാമ്ധിദ്ഥ മഡാഥിയഥമല ലിവ
Whoa, whoa. Hold on there, boss.
ധാ. നാഥ ഡ്വേ, ത്ഥ
Those Caterpillar kids need someone to play with.
8ധദ്മ്ലാധഠ്ല്ധ്ടവാലഥഥടേടധ ഉാലിധിത്ഥ ടടടലംറ ധിധാല്നമ്ഥ
But my friends don't belong there.
ചാ മാറിയ മിവ ലിം നമലട ലമി ഠിടമമ
None of us do, I agree.
11509 ടില്വാ റിമ 10, ലിവ ടല്ഡ്ധ
Which is why, for the good of our community,
ടലാദ്വാ ധി, ധിധഘാലിത്ിധസ്ധബ് ന്മ...
we ask the newer toys, the stronger ones,
ബി ബു നല്നന ൮9 ധാമം ൮9 ലാവ...
to take on the hardships the rest of us can't bear anymore.
നല്ദിധി ദടധിദ്വ ൮9 മി ലിം ദ്പ്വാമഥാധഥ്നാ
Well, I guess that makes sense.
ചവ ടാ ധ ണാടധിം ഖിയ
But I can't accept. We're a family. We stay together.
ലാ മിവ മലാല ണനലലിനബ. രദ ടദഡ ലധലാാ. ൭ നല ലാലടാണമ
Family man, huh? I understand.
ലമി 1ല്ധാമ, ൭? ചവ നല്ണ
Put him back in the timeout chair.
ലററ ഠി 1ാ21॥0ി। ബട ധ്വയണമ്
What are ya... Unhand me!
1ലാദടിയ്ഥ മഡ്‌
Bring in the Bookworm.
ഗ്മ നാടധിറധ ദധിവ
Here it is.
111]
It was filed under "Lightyear."
1൩൭ വ്ല്വിദ്ഥ ധാമ "1ബ0വടമ്ല്‌
Let's see here.
കുധഠിട്ബ
“Accessories. Maintenance.” Here we go.
- 1] 1-111-11 -1125%1:111:-1:18
“Remove screws to access battery compartment.”
ീഠഠ്‌ നണം. മമഥ 83ലി
What are you doing?
൧3൮9 ദ്വ 1മിഡിത്ന?
Stop!
ലിത്‌
Let go of me!
1ലാദടിയ്ഥ മിഡ്‌ ഠ്‌
“To return your Buzz Lightyear action figure to its original factory settings..."
“0 1ഘമ്പാലി॥ത്ഥ ഥമ 10൨൮ലെ മധ ലട... ൮ഠ പഥ വിമാ ൭51...
No!
ലവര്ഥ ടധിട ദ്്ലി ണമ്ന്‌ 1൪ ലനം” ഗിച്നഥണം
Stop! No! No! No!
ലല! നിഴല
-What was that? -Sounds like it came from the hall.
്യാഠഡ? ഒബ്ര ട്രാ മററ ചി ഡാഥാസ്ധ
I'll see what it was.
ചവ ലിര്ബ്വാലിദബമ
What do you see? Anything?
൧3൮9 ദ്വ 111൫90 ഷഡാ-പ്യാമ?
No, just a dark hallway and... Wait. Wait!
121 മബ൩൭ ഡമി ലാലിദ്വ റ്മ-- ധനാ. സനാ!
I see Andy!
ചവ മ്പാമിധഥഥഠ്‌
-What? -That's impossible.
്വാമ? 117111]
No, no, I really see him. In his room.
12%, മിവ ലാല്ാലല നമമ്പാമിറിമ. ഉ॥॥॥॥ന്ൃ൭
My other eye! The one I left behind.
നിമ മിവ ടലാലല്‍ല മാ! 9 പവ ഗാദിത്ഥ
This is so weird. He's packing up.
ബാല്യ മലി. ൧1൭ ടലറഠ്ദണാ ാലിനണമടട
Here comes Buster. Out of the way! Get away!
ബി ഠി ദ്ദ 3ധട്ല 1(ലലാ॥! ലാ!
Okay, Andy's out in the hall.
ചിറി, ഗദ്ബലാമെ്ദട ബാഗ മസ്ധ.
He's looking in the attic.
൧1 നലല 14ഠില്‍ 8ധിവ
Wait, there's Mom. Why is he so upset?
ധനാ, ധ ഠി ണമ 1ലദ്വാ റിദ ണമ?
Oh, no! Oh, this is terrible!
൨ ॥ിദ്ചറ ഠവബ്‌ ലയി!
He's looking for us. Andy's looking for us!
൧1 നലല്വി 1൩2. ൧൧൦൮ നല്ലി 10
He's looking for us?
1 നല്ലി ന്മ?
So Andy does want us. I knew it! I just knew it!
1-1 11:1111-111:111:11:1 111 ചവ റ മഠ വവ ദ്ദ ാറ്റമറ
I think he did mean to put us in the attic.
വ മട റിദ ണന ൫910 നടടധിറമ്ഥ ന൯൫ 1൭ ലബാ
Well, then, Woody was telling the truth.
77000൮ ലാല മിഷ്വാലാലദ്ല
-Holy cow! -And you didn't believe him.
1:11: ബദ്ധ മിധാലമ്യേമിത്ഥ ഠി
Hey, you didn't believe him first!
ദ്ധ ൮൭ മലാല ദ്വേമിദ്ഥ ഠിദ ഠ്ധിധ്‌
Guys, we gotta... We gotta go home!
രവ 009, 10 നടട॥--ഗ്മ നടടി ാധിമനാ!
-Lotso! -Hey, there.
ല്‍ റിടമനാ.
How y'all doin’ this fine evenin'?
൧3 നല്ല വസ്ഡ ടലസ്ധ ലാലി?
Thank goodness! Have you seen Buzz?
൨, നടാ ാപിവധ്ധ ഠ്ദ ല്വാല ഒധമമ?
There's been a mistake. We have to go.
൧03 1൭ട॥ല്ലാമഥ. 0൭ നടട ലാലി
Go? Why, you just got here. In the nick of time, too.
ലി? (ധാമ ടമമ്വാലി ലാമ വാഠ്മ നട.
We were runnin’ low on volunteers for the little ones.
ബി റ 1ല്ഡമാമ ടധ്ന്ധലിമധ ധഴിധത്ഥല്ലത്ഥല്ലശം॥!
They just love new toys, now, don't they?
സീലല്യ ടധിയിമറ നല്നമഥ ലാല, ലാധിത്ഥ?
“Love"? We've been chewed, kicked, drooled on.
ട്ധിമിരന? ബി ഠി1ഠ9191%, വ്ഭഥഠ്മാ, വിധേ
Just look at my pocketbook!
110 മധിമ്പാധിവ രല ലിഡ്‌
Well, here's the thing, sweet potato. You ain't leavin’ Sunnyside.
ബി ാലിത്ഥമ ടലാലലുര, ടയ ദ്ധ മഖിറദത്ഥ നാദിര്ഥ ടധ്ബുടിേ
“Sweet potato"! Who do you think you're talking to?
ടൃ! രവ ന॥ന്നലിര്ധ ലാലിയ 0൩ ടില്വാമ?
I have over 30 accessories, and I deserve more respect...
എവ നലമ്പാഥബതി ലാ ഠ്‌ 30 മീദടടം॥ി ദ്ദ മിവ മധിലാ ന്നംന്ണനമ--
That's better.
1ധിലാവാല
Hey, no one takes my wife's mouth, except me.
121 റിദ ടില്വാ 0 ാഠിലി ബാ! സ്ഥി ടലി മിവ, ഭേ! മിവ
Give it back, you furry air freshener!
1ല്ബാലി॥ഭ്നബതം, ാലഗമററ। ധഠ്മമലാലാധ്ധ!
Come on, guys. We're goin’ home.
കൃധി. ഖി നലിലാധിമാ
Whoa there, missy.
8ലനല്നി ഠിടാഥമ, വിധ
You're not goin’ anywhere.
ദ്വ ലിറശ്ഥ ണന
Oh, yeah? And who's gonna stop us?
ബത? ഉമ്ഥ ടില്വാ 9 മമ നല്ലി ന്മ?
Buzz! You're back!
8ധമമ! ദല റ ല്ബാല॥!
Look out!
1120-02!
Prisoners disabled, Commander Lotso!
ദാഥഠ്ധാറ റ്മുടിരറ, ഠനമഥഠ്ല ടം!
-Buzz, what are you doing? -Silence, minions of Zurg!
-8ധമമ, ലാമ൮9 ധ ദ്വിര്ഥ? -21ണ, 7൭1൮൭ മധ!
You're in the custody of the Galactic Alliance!
1111 11:11-11] ലടല്ധഡമറ ദില്വിറ
-"Zurg"? -"Galactic Alliance"?
ലെടല്ഡഡമറ ദലില്വിദ
Oh, boy.
൨, മി്മനമം
Good work, Lightyear. Now, lock 'em up!
ലു ാഠറ്റട, 190൮ലെ. ട്ല്ദ്മാ, വസ്ഥാധത്ഥ നലല!
Yes, sir!
മ, ഡമ്‌
Where do you think you're going?
൧3൮9 ദ്വ 1മിഡിത്ന?
Buzz! We're your friends!
-]21%:1111॥ 1-111-11]!
Spare me your lies, temptress.
പറ്റാനാ മവ, 0ലുഠംഠ്മ
Your emperor's defeated,
മ്യമിദ്ധ ലിമ ദിലഗമടിത്ഥ
and I'm immune to your bewitching good looks.
ദ്ദ മിവ 13! ബണശംദന്നിത്ലിര്ധ
Hey, Mongo! Keep your paws off my wife!
റല ഗീംണാഠ! ൧വത്ഥ മാമ ത്ധ ഠി ടലി ലിഡ്‌
Hey! Let go of me, you drooling doofus!
1ലാമടിയ്ഥ മിവ, 0ഠഠിഠവ
Not him.
8ധിത്ഥ 1൭.
I think this potato needs to learn himself some manners.
ചവ ടാ ദഹമ്ഥാബ്ബ്‌ ബട റില്ല ടപ്വാനമ്ഥ
Take him to the box.
ദാ ഠി ദ രലി്വയ
Hey! Put me down, you moron! Where are you taking me?
7 ്ധബിത്ഥ മിവ, ലാംഠ്ഠവ! ദ്ധ നലിലാമ മിവ ദ ണമ?
Bad baby! Bad baby!
51.71 1:111:1151.711:111:14
Ken? What's going on?
14൦? ൧3൮9 ടലഠ്ണാലാലില്വ?
Barbie! I told you to wait in the Dream House.
ചവ ഠ്11ടധ്ധ്വത്ധ ഡാ ഠി ബന്ന.
What are you doing to my friends?
൧3൮9 വ 1മിഡിത്ഥ ാഠ്ദ ഡാറ്റ ലിവ?
Get in there!
സീടടധി റിന ടല!
-Barbie, wait! -Don't touch me.
81:15]! 00 ടബഡധി മിവ.
-We're through! -Barbie! I did...
[പ റ ടലിടടല!!
And give me my scarf back!
ഉാഥ ഘമ്പാലത്ഥ ടിയ്‌ ച്ഡ്‌
Lightyear! Explain our overnight accommodations.
1111: 1:1111:1:1111.11:1111:-]
Sir, yes, sir! Prisoners sleep in their cells.
ധാ, ൭, ഡബ്‌ ദ്ധ മിഥ ഴിഠ്ധ ഠി ടല നലലര
Any prisoner caught outside their cell spends the night in the box.
സീന ാറര്‍്ധ യായ 1ധല് ടല സ്ഥിധാലന്നലി്മണ ദിസ്രലം
Roll call at dusk and dawn.
8ലിവഡമ്പാധി ഠി ഡ്യിഡ ടല ഠ്‌ ടധാധ..
Any prisoner misses roll call, spends the night in the box.
നീണ്ട ാഥര്‍്ധണ ഗാലി റാലി ാലന്നമിമന ദിന രല
Prisoners do not speak unless spoken to.
ദ്ധ മിലാംല്ലാലലിയ്ാ ധി ഠി ടം.
Any prisoner talks back, spends the night...
ദ്ധ വനനലല ലിദ്ധലാലന്നമിമണ..
In the box! We get it.
ഉിമണ ല്ല ല്മണ..!
At ease, soldier. They're neutralized.
വില, മടി. സിലലര ൭0 ്നലത്ചിടാടിര്ഥ
But remember, they'll say anything to make you doubt yourself.
ചവ 09൭, ന്0ിം ഖിത്ഥ ത്ര ല്വാദ ടദ്വദ ധഴിധാധമിര്ബമശ്ധ ടട ദ്ലര്ധ
Don't worry, Commander.
പറ ലട, (ഗനമഥഠ്ല
Any doubt I had got pounded out of me at the academy.
൧3 ടദ്യട ടട ൮9 ലിവ മ്മ ഠി മട ഠി മിരഠില്സ്‌
Listen up, folks.
ഉല്ല ട്ബി, വധ ൦൭൧൭..
We got a way of doin’ things here at Sunnyside.
[പ്ര ഠി മേ നലദിയഡത്ഥ ടടടധധഠിട്ല്‍
If you start at the bottom, pay your dues,
മിമധ ദ്ധ ലാല്ധിദ ദ്വാമഡമ, ലി] ൦൭ട..
life here can be a dream come true!
ബിധ്വോ ഠിട്ബ്‌ ലാം ടാഡ സ്വിബ്‌!
But if you break our rules, step outta line,
ചവ മിദ്ധ ദ്ധി, മിധാലിശില്വമബാലി.
try to check out early, well, you're just hurtin’ yourselves.
ധാമ ലാട ഠി0.. ദ്ധ 0൨൩൭ നബി ദലര്ധവ ടലി
Woody! What did you do to him?
൧70൦0൮ 4൮3 ൮9 മല ാധമാ3ഠിമ വിമ?
You all get a good night's rest.
ദ്രസ്ധ ടലസ്ധാ ദിഠ്ധിലി ര്‍്ണ ബബ.
You got a full day of playtime tomorrow.
ദ്ധ ഠി നട നല്‌ ൮9 ലാബ്ഥി ടട
1225 Syca...
ടാഡ, ധാ, ധോ, നമ, ടു... േ..
Who's Velocistar237?
ട്ല്വാദ ഗലിംല്ട്ല 237?
That's just a dinosaur toy down the street.
1ധ മ൩൭ നമിറ ദ്0ഠടദഥ 1 1111111:11:11:111
That's nothing. Let me just take care of that.
- 1] 1111-1:111:1 ദില മിവ ധഡടിമബ൭..
-Just a dinosaur. -All right.
11൩൭ ടലലധ॥ റിനഠടമഥ
Sycamore. Okay, enter!
൭൮..മേ..ന൦൦.. 32311021, ലിത്ബ്‌
Please don't be far. Please, please!
1010 ൃണബ്൮)3ധ1.. 7൦1൦09, 01൦0!
Right around the corner? It's right around the corner!
ലയ ടിബി ടല്]മ? 1൩൮൭ ലയ ടിബി ടല്യല!
I'm going to college! Look at me! I'm big toy on campus! Hello!
ചവ ലിദ്ഥ ദ രില! 00 ലിഡ്‌ ചവ നമ്നബാടടല് റിദ്വ്പാധട! ലിം!
-Hey, I'll see you at the sock hop. -Okay, Potsie.
വ മിരബ്ധ്വാ ദ്ധ ഠിനലിട മി. 8211020൨, ം്ടില..
Hey, listen. If any of you guys ever get to Sunnyside Daycare,
ലാല... !(യിമ്ധ ടടടില്വാദ റമി വസ്ധ ടബ്പാമി ൭ ലടദ്ധ്മമമ്ഥ ടധ്യടിര്‍്ടേ..
you tell 'em Woody made it home.
ദ്ധാല്യ്ഡ ണ്ഡ റമ ലാധിമനറ.
-You came from Sunnyside? -But how'd you escape?
“ര്ധ ഠ്യ ഠി ട്ടി? “ലവി ാമറുമ്നമന ന്ധ ിലാടടിര്റ ഠി?
Well, it wasn't easy.
120 സ്വഠ്മ്ബ വിവ...
What do you mean "escape"?
ഗ്വാ ണമദ്ധാ ത്വ "ചിത്ഥ ലീ?
Sunnyside is a place of ruin and despair.
ട്ധനബുടിര്‍്ടേ സ്വാ റാലി ശസ്ധടമ്മ ദ്ദ ഭടലഠി മഥ
Ruled by an evil bear who smells of strawberries.
3: 1:11: 11:11: ൮9 ലാല്നദ്ധ ട്നമഗീാലി
The guy may seem plush and huggable on the outside,
ലിലി ധ മന്വാല്ംട്രാലാല ദ്മവാഠിലി ദ്ലാല്ധം വിധ ജ്വാി! ഠിരിന..
but inside, he’s a monster.
013 ടല ആിഭമടമ
But... How do you know that?
ദാഠുഖ്നാനാ ദ്ധ മധ
Chuckles. He'll tell you.
്ഡംഠടട.. ൧012 മിരബാലി്യ്ഡിര്ധ
Yeah, I knew Lotso.
൭, മിവ ഥമ 1 ഠട൦..
He was a good toy. A friend.
1 നല്‌ ൮9 ലാലി. ടം രബ
Me and him, we had the same kid, Daisy.
൧ിവ ഠ്മഥ വാ, ബ്‌ ദബ്॥॥ന ാധഠില്റയ ടമണമ, ഉദ്ിടു
1 was there when Lotso got unwrapped.
ചവ ലാലമഠ്മ ഠി ടമാ നട ാഥററിവടമ ടം റ॥ധി൨..
Daisy loved us all.
ഉചിട ടയറിന്‌ യ്‌ ടലസ്ധമ..
But Lotso,
ചാ ॥ഠ1ടഠ,
Lotso was special.
1ഠടഠ [ധ ടന...
They did everything together.
സീലല്ര മിഡിത്ഥ ടമ്മ രാലടമനാ
You've never seen a kid and a toy more in love.
ദ്ധ ഖിലാലനമ 110൩2 ടം വാധഠ്ല ദമ നമ്നാബാലറിയ റിസ നേ
One day, we took a drive.
ടമധ മല, തമ്പലാലടില..
Hit a rest stop. Had a little playtime.
ല്ലി 01 രഥടമ്ഥ ലീമ... ഒലന്നമ്ന 'ഷ്ല്വാ
After lunch, Daisy fell asleep.
ലാട നല്വ്ഥ ലററ ധി, ഉലട ലിഠ്ധ..
She never came back.
1 ലിലാധി..
Lotso wouldn't give up.
1ഠടഠ 11 മി ണബലമ യില
it took forever, but we finally made it back to Daisy's.
1ബ൭ മമ്പാ॥ നട ൮9 ണമ 'ല്വി മ്വ്ണ്ുര
But by then, it was too late.
ദ്ധ ാധമ ടല്ദണബ൭.. ചാ 0ാ3ഠിമ നാട ധ, [ബര ൭൨ ലിഷ
Something changed that day inside Lotso.
ടടധാഡ ാലഡാമ ലി ധ ദിന ഠി ॥ഠടം..
Something snapped.
ടടധാഡ സ്ധടബ
She replaced us. Come on!
൧19 ല൭0 ബിന... ചവ
-No, she only replaced you! -She replaced all of us.
“121 ഠി 0൫൭൩൫൭ േസധിര്ബത്ധ! 212 റമബിദ്ഥ ന്ന ടല്ധമ,ലാധിത്ന?
She don't love you no more!
൧1൭ ലിം ടമ ര്ധ ദാ!
Now come on!
1ഠിംഘ്റിമ്വ
We were lost. Cast off. Unloved. Unwanted.
ബി ടടടമ.. വിത്‌ 110 ല്ടമയമ!.. നി ല്വാലിധിത്
Then we found Sunnyside.
1ലസ്ധഠിദറ യ ധമ്പാല ട്ടി.
But Lotso wasn't my friend anymore.
ലാ ॥ഠ1ടഠാധിമറ 1൭൮ രല ലിവ
He wasn't anyone's friend.
ഉ ദ്ധ! നല്ബപമഠി। മഗ ടടടില്ലാമ
He took over Sunnyside and rigged the whole system.
൧ മമ്പാ॥-0 ദി ട്ടി ദമ നലറ്ധിയ ടല്ധഡി ടിട്ണ
So how'd you get out?
പ്9ഠി.. ാമുല്നമനാ ത്വ ിലാടടിര്ഥ ഠര്‍്ലീ?
I got broke. Bonnie found me, took me home.
ചവ ദ്വി. 8ംബില്വധ്പാമി മിവ, ലാസ മിവ ലാധ്ഥാ
Other toys, they weren't so lucky.
നിന !മ്ന, ന0ിറിഠ്ല്ധാല്റ്ധലാലനടടാ ലാമ!
It ain't right what Lotso done. New toys,
1ലിധാലധി പ്വാ൮9 1ഠട൦ം 1മഡിര൨.. ീല്നമഥ ാമ,
they don't stand a chance.
നലല മിധാനല്ധഥാ
-But my friends are in there. -You can't go back.
“ദ്വ യമ മിവലാലമഠ്ട ഠി ടമ്മ ര്ധ യി ടമ്മ.
Returning now would be suicide!
ലെ ടിനാ ടാ നലമ്പാഥഗ്ധി ദല
But what about your Andy?
ചാ ാുലനാനാ 0... ൧ഗദിര്ധ?
Isn't he leaving for college?
ധി ഠി ലിലാലയ!.. ൨ രീല?
Quiet, musical hog! Knock it off!
ഉന, മ്പനലലാലന്നമ്ന സ്ധമലിറ ലില്‍
Oh, Bullseye. I miss Woody, too.
൨ ദധിടലുട.. ചി്വ്ധാഠ ബനഠിത്ഥ ഗം
But he ain't ever comin’ back.
ലവ 19 ലിറ ശമ്ബാമ!..
Rise and shine, campers!
കററ ദ്മ്ബരാലടില്വാ, ദ്ധ മാ!
Commander Lotso, sir!
.ഠനമറഠ്ല ടം, ഡമ്‌
All quiet, nothing to report.
ടലസ്ഡാബമ ടി, വിറ ല്വാ ധിം ഠി॥ലാംിത്ഥ
Excellent, Lightyear. Come on. We need ya back at Star Command.
ലാമ, 100൨ലെ... ഷഡ്‌ ബി ാലിധിത് ദ്ധ ഭ്ബാലി॥
Wait! What've you done with my husband?
ധാ! ഡാ ലി ത്ധില്ഡിത്ഥ ാഠ്ദ ടധമമബി മിവ?
Sweetheart!
ടൃ!
It was cold and dark. Nothing but sand and a couple of Lincoln Logs.
1ബ൭ ടല്ധിധ്മഥ ലാ.
I don't think those were Lincoln Logs.
എവ ടാഡ ാധിത്ഥ 0൦0൩0൦95...
You all get ready. You got a play-date with destiny!
ദ്രസ്ധ ടലസ്ധലാലടിമ്വാ. ദ്രസ്ധ ഠ്ദ ല്ധ്ബ। ഠ്ണണ ദ്ശ്ഥല്‌
Hello?
ലിം?
You shouldn't have come back, cowboy.
ദ്ധ ഖിധാമഡധ്‌ഷ്പാമി! 1ലാം!..
They've cracked down hard since you left. More guards, more patrols.
സിലലര ലി നാതിത്ഥ ടലഡ് ടല്മ്ധിര്ധ ലാലി...
You and your friends ain't ever getting out of here now.
ദ്ധ ഠ്യ ിര്ധ ലിറ്ഥ റ്രാധിഘ്ധല മി ടബ്‌ ടിനാ
I made it out once.
ചവ പാലന ഘ്ധല ടലയി॥.
You got lucky once. Want my advice?
ദ്ധ ലാലണമടിാ വാമി ടലി ധ പലി മടിമ ലിവ
Keep your heads down. You'll survive.
ഉ॥ബ്ിദ്ഥ ഠ0.. ദ്ധ ലിദ്ഥ ബ്ധോ
Yeah, for how long?
വര, ധരിലാലയാദ ണമ?
I've been here years.
ചവ റ്മ്വാല്യ്ഡ നബ വ്ട്ബി
They'll never break me.
സില്ലി ലിറശ്ഥ ദ്ല്വാമാ്ബ്ത്ഥ ലിവ...
There's only one way toys leave this place.
11ബമ 09 ടമഡ മേ നമ ാഠില നാമി ല്പാമബ
Poor fella. Trash truck comes at dawn.
ടട ഠ19.. ലി ട്വാലി ടമാ ഡച്ഡ ടധാഥ
Then it's off to the dump.
1ലസ്ധഠിമ 1൭ മിര്ഥ 1 ലമ്പാമലാധമറുമന ടമ്മ.
Look, I appreciate your concern, old-timer.
ചവ ലാലി ശ്ധിടദ്ധമബത്ധം, ൦009 1൭൩൭..
But we have a kid waiting for us. Now, we're leaving.
ചാ മി നലസ്ധാധസമി ടല വധഠ്ലി ൮9 ന്ഥ രബ. ഖി ല്ദ്ഥ ാലയ॥..
If you'd help us, one toy to another, I'd sure be grateful.
ദ്രിദ്ധ ദ്വ ദാല്‍ നല്പാഥഡ ബി...
Well, if you're gonna get out,
ദ്രിദ്ധ ദ്വ നല്ലല്ലിത്ഥ ഠ0..
first thing you gotta get through's the doors.
ചാല ലാലമനാ ര്ധാല്ധ മിധിത്ഥ 1: 1111:11111111 1:
Locked, every night. Inside and out. Keys are left on a hook in the office.
ഉ॥ധ0൦.. ടഖിദ്വ നമ്ലസ! 21[:1:11:1111 1111111117
Got it. What else?
ചല ക്വ 1917
Lotso has trucks patrolling all night long.
1ഠടഠ നലമ്പാഥബയി മ ൮9 മ 7൦0ഠ്മമഥ ടലാമബ്ണാ ന്മ്മണ
Hallway, lobby, playground.
ദ്ധ ലാല, 1, മനബലാലന്നമ്നമ൨..
Yeah, yeah, yeah. What about the wall?
൫൭. ദാല്നാനാ ഗണ ഗണ?
Eight-feet high. Cinder block. No way through it.
8 ൭0 നാബര.. ടിന ലാധ മഥ 1210 ഠ്മ്യമിമ നല്ല്ധ്സത.
You go over or under.
ദ്ധ നടി ॥ഡ മട ദ്ധ ലാമ
That's it? Doesn't seem so bad.
1ധ ടദ്യമ? നലിധാല്ഡ ലഡഡ.
it's not. Your real problem's the monkey.
11൭1. സീടടമില ടലാലല ദ്ധ 1൭൨ നംസ%
The monkey's the eye in the sky.
സീം 5൨ നര ദമ.
He sees everything.
1 ഗ്വാ ടലി ബമ
Classrooms.
81॥॥ധദട..
Hallways.
ദ്ധ ലല...
Even the playground.
“ലന്നമടധി മണ ലാല്നമ്നല
You can unlock doors, sneak past guards, climb the wall,
ദ്ധ ാഠിലവാധിര വാഡ, ഗേ 1ല്ധദ്ധ ര്‍്ലാല്ഖിത്ാ ലാമി ..ഥദബ റ്നഠ്നാ..
but if you don't take out that monkey, you ain't going nowhere.
ചവ മിദ്ധ ദ്വ ഖിംസ്ധടമ്ബത്ഥ നംബ൦ധ, ദ്ധ ഖിദ്മ ണമ
You wanna get out of here? Get rid of that monkey!
ദ്ധ നലില്ഷ്ധല ദ്ദ്ലി ടബ്‌? ്ല്ലാധടിമറ ണംബ൭ഡി
Recess! Come on, kids!
ഗീമടമ ലമ സീമലിമ൨,ധമ്പോധകചറ
Hey, guys.
ദില, ദ്ധ ൦0൭..
-Hey, hey, hey, buddy! -Thank goodness!
ലി, മഗ്മവ്‌ പ്വഒടാ 3110
-You're alive! -Course I'm alive!
“ര്മധ നട വ്ദ്ധാ! ടറി ഡ ല്വ ബ്ഠ്വോ!
Hey, my hat! Wait, where's Buzz?
ല്‍... ലാ മവ! സനാഠല, നമാ 8ധമമ?
Lotso did something to him!
1ഠടഠ 02% ടലടധമധ ലാമി ദില!
He thinks he's a real Space Ranger again.
1 നിഗ ഠി ൭൨൮൭൧ ബ്ല ൧നാ1൭ട ടലി 1൭91
-Oh, no. -Oh, yes.
01, ലിഠ്ച്റ 0, ൮൭..
Return of the astro-nut.
1ല്പാലിന൭ ഥറിരടമഗ 9
Woody, we were wrong to leave Andy. I was wrong.
പ്ര ടിലാ ലബ്ദി ൧ഥഠ.. ചവ ടമ്മ
Jessie's right, Woody. She was wrong.
8ലഡി ലിഷ്വാ ടടടില.. ൧1 ടമ്മ
No, no, it's my fault for leaving you guys.
ച്പണ ടമില മിവ ലയ നല്നാമിദ്നത്ധ
From now on, we stick together.
ീധില! ടലദ്ഥമററ, 1൭ ല്ല ാലടമനട..
But Andy's leavin’ for college.
ചാ ൧0൨ മിഥ 1൪ ശില...
College? Hog-tie the mailman!
14ഠില? ഷനി
We gotta get you home before Andy leaves tomorrow!
[പമ ണടട ലാമ ത്വ ാധിദ ടലാല്ധന ൧൧ ലാലി ടം!
Tomorrow? But that means...
ടം നചാ। ധ ണനമിദ്ധബ..
It means we're busting out of here, tonight.
1-1 11:11: 11:11 ദ്ക്0ി ടബ്‌. നീലിമണ ബ്‌...
-What? Impossible! -But there's no way out of here!
യാമ? ്ധട്യ്പ॥! “ദ്വ മ ഠ്യ്വമ്മറ ഷ്ധല ദ്ദ ടബ്‌!
No, there is one way out.
12% മഠ ടദഡ്ദ്മ ശ്ധല.
One way.
ടാഡ...
Okay, here's what we're gonna do.
ബ്ിമ൨൮൭ ല്ല മിഡത്ഥ..
-Springy dog. -Present.
ബിനാ ട്രാ? -119017..
Green guys.
ലിലി വ്വമ്ധ?
-Cowgirl. -Here.
101001 ഉലലമ്പാധമല..
Horse.
1ഠ9..
-Piggy bank. -Yo.
“ചാധനാ ട്‌സ്വാനമല..
-Tyrannosaurus. -Here.
“ൃമബഠടദ്ധസഡട..
-Barbie.
-8ദലാ1ല..
Hey! Hey! Tuberous root-man! Wake up!
ദില! ല്ല്വാലയിയ ഡല്‌ ദഒദാധ്ബ്‌
Impossible!
്ധടമ്വ॥!
Little late for a stroll, eh, Potato Head?
“ലില്ധബ്പാ ധിധാലടില, ലി, 7൭൦ 11൦?
That's Mr. Potato Head to you, smoothie.
1ധ 65൨. ൦൦൭൧൦ ॥11ല3ഠ്‌ 039൭ ൭൨, ാഠഠ്ഠ1..!
Well, well, well. You're turning out to be quite the troublemaker, aren't you?
ദ്ധ ബി ഠ ടലണമിന്ന 4901 നാടല്,ാധിത്ന?
What did you think you were gonna do? Waltz right out of here?
൧൮ ദ്ധ നിന ദ്ധ മില്ല്ഡിര്? സിലി 1ല്ധല മലി ടലി?
Yeah, and I would've got away with it, too,
൮൫൭ ദ്ദ മിവ ലഡഡ ാല്ദട വിദ്ധാധിര്ഥ ലമ നല്ല ര്ധദനലവയ്വാധിറ
You ascot-wearing pink-noser!
ദ്ധ ബി ാബസാധിറ
You're not a toy! You're an accessory!
ര്ധാധിര്ഥ നമി! രവ ബി ല്ദടേടംല്‌!
You're a purse with legs.
11111111 -11:1:111 15111110
Take him back to the box.
ദാ ഠി ശ്ബാലി। ൨ 1ഠാലല്ധ
No! No, not the box! I'm sorry. I didn't mean it! I like ascots.
നിറ നിഠ്മ്ലാധിമഥ ഠില്ഡ്‌ ലിവ മിവ...
Really. No, no, no!
ദധി! നച ദ്മിം ലി്ല്റ
Okay, check.
ച്ചി, ധ്വട..
Good work, Lightyear. All right, resume your space-guy-thingy.
ലി ാമറ്ധട, 100വ൮൭െ.. 810, ലട ഡാടട ാരടമമ്ധ
Yes, sir, well-groomed man!
൭, ഡമ, ല്ലിന൮൭ ടലി
What do you want?
൧൧3൮9 ദ്ധ നല
I can't take it here, Ken. l wanna go to the Butterfly Room. With you!
ചവ മി0്രാ0 നലലമ് ഭഠ്ദമ്ഥ ഠി ടബ്‌...
Yeah, well, you should've thought of that yesterday.
വര, ദ്വ ടലാദധന്ുര നിഗ്ധിതബ൭ ടനണമിമണ..
I was wrong.
ചവ ടദിമ്വ
I wanna be with you, Ken, I do. In your Dream House.
ചവ മിലാലടാമണട ദ്വ 1൭൨, നനനമന.. ഠ്വ ിര്ധ
Please take me away from this! Take me away!
101൦09 ലാസ മിവ ദ്ദ0ി ടബ്‌! ഗ്മ മിവ ലാലി!
Darn it, Barbie!
ഫ്ന മലാല
Okay, but things are complicated around here.
810൭0 യവ 1ഠ്മ്ഥ ഡ്പ്ിട്ബ..
-You gotta do what I say. -I will, Ken! I promise!
ര്മധ നടട്ി ॥൮ ലിവ്വാ മിവ... വിവ ടല്ധ്വധ! ഡ്മ!
Wait. I'll do anything! I'll change your diapers!
ധാ! വിവ മിത്ബാധമ ല്വാട ടദ്യല! ചവ ലിദ്ഥ ഡിദ്ധല്ധ്ബിതഥ്‌
Go get the tape!
ലു.. ്ല്ാദിയഥ.. 115
And this is where the magic happens.
മഥ ഠിട്ബിലി ന॥ധാലില്വ
Look at all your clothes!
11:11 1111-11-11 11
I can't believe you never brought me up here!
ചവ മലാല വ്ധ ലിാലന്സഡാമഗമ മിവ ശഭ മട ടലി!
-Tennis whites? Mission to Mars! -I know, I know, I know.
ദ്യ ബട? ഗിട। ൭ ഗീലട! വ മധ..
Check this out! Kung fu fighting.
0മ്ിമ് ബി! ലിമ വറ,
Campus hero with matching sports pennant, huh?
റല വ്വ്വാധട.. ദി്ബാല്യ ടധിര്ഥ ൮9 ൧3, ബ്ന?
Flower power! Oh, Ken!
ളച്യധാധനാല
No one appreciates clothes here, Barbie. No one.
121 ഠി ടില്വാ 3 നല്ലു! മിയി ഠിട്ബ ന്ദ്‌ ടില്ാമ..
Ken, would you model a few outfits for me?
8ഠിലി മിധമ്ധലാലമാാല്ത്ഥ ാലാലല്വാ ഉമ്മ ധിം ലിവ?
Just a few?
11ബമ ലാലാല്ല്വാമ?
Go get the key.
ഉല റ്ല്വാിമറ വന...
Where is it, where is it?
സീ റിമ?
Where's the key? Where's the key? Bingo!
ഗീ ധ്രു? ദാം!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
ദ്ധ 7൨0 ലാമ ദ്ധ ധാ
I told you, keep your hands off of my stuff!
(മഥ മിവ ലാലിയ ശ്വ, 11:11 111 1:111:10-111:1:1111111
Make a move, porky!
ഗാലി, ടി ന്മ ന്ധി
Hey, hey, hey! No fighting! Break it up!
1-111:1:111 1111111111
-Hey! Hey! -Take that, walnut-brain.
൧മ്പാ॥ ധ, മഡ്‌.
No wonder you're extinct.
ഉഡധി്പമ്വ ദ ാധ്വാധട
Hey, you can't hit each other. That's my job!
ദ്ധ ഖിധാംല ടിന ാലസ്ധ്പാധിം. 1ധ ഡാടട ലിഡ്‌!
Help! Prison riot!
101൦0൭! €ലമ്പാലഠബ്ലിന്ഥ ലാല്ല!
Get the tortilla.
ഉല്ദ്ധിത്ഥ ഗനിദ..
-Ready? -Ready.
-ടലറിമ? -5ലറി൭..!
No more games, Ken! What did Lotso do to Buzz?
121 നമിധാലനനദ്ധ ദാ! ൧3൮9 1015൦ 1൭1ഡിശ൨ ലാറി 8ധമമ?
And how do we switch him back?
ഉല ാഠറല്നാഥട നമ ൫910 ഡിയ ഠി ശമ്ബപാല?
You can't make me talk. You can't!
ദ്ധ മിധാംല്ഡാധമിര്ഥ മിവാലദവന്വാ..
But I'd like to see you try.
ചാ। മവ നാബമലര്ധ നണഥധോഃ
Let's see. Hawaiian surf trunks.
നീച !സന൯ 10. ടല്ധല നലോ ദ്യ
Barbie! Those were vintage!
൨, ദദബ്ധല ധ ഗ്ല!
It's okay. All right, go ahead, rip ‘em, I don't care.
12% ല്വാമ.. "ലട, രുദ്രം മിവ ഖിധറ്ടമ..
They're a dime a dozen.
സീലല്ര സ്മ റമ ടലാഥറ ഠി ദേ...
Glitter tux.
1 ധിദലഠ്ം നല.
Who cares? Who cares? Sequins are tacky. Who cares?
ട്രല്വാമ1റ്ടമ? ടിച്വാ!റ്ടമ? ടല്ഡല മഠം. ടില്വാ ടമ?
A Nehru jacket.
പഠി ലംബ...
Barbie! Not the Nehru.
ലാല, ധി ലവ്‌!
This is from what, 1967?
ബി ചി ജന ല്വാദ, 1967?
The groovy formal collection, yes!
1ഠിലട്രി "ംന്നമി ൮9 ലായ!
-What a shame. -Oh, no, no, no! No!
ഥി ടല. 0 റ്റ
There's an instruction manual!
൧ വാധ്വ ഉാമറദ്ധമബല്‍!
Lotso switched Buzz to Demo mode!
1ഠടഠ ണനലദ്ധിദ്വ 8ധമമ 1൭ നഠഠ്‌ ഠ്ലനം!
Where's that manual?
സീമ ാധിവലാഥഠ്ധബധ?
I don't know why this couldn't wait until morning, Ken,
ചവ മ മ്ഡശ്ധദ്വാ [ബ്‌ മധാം1ല൨ ഡാ ബ്നാദേ ഠി, ൭൨,
but here you go.
'ല്വിബിഠ്ട
What's takin’ so doggone long?
1ലദ്വാ മണ ടാ
So how do we fix Buzz?
ദാഠുല്നാനാ !ന്൯ നമ്ധാലാലിറ 8ഒധമമ?
What are you looking at, feathers?
൧3൮ ദ്ധ ലാദഥ്ണാ, ാധ്ധ?
Yeah, fly away, you coward.
൭, ബാഡഘ്ിമ്വലാലാടധേ്‌ ൨0-൦൨.
Well, that's just great.
്ലാദ്ധിബധ..
Help! Prison riot!
101൦0൭! €ലമ്പാലഠബ്ലിന്ഥ ലാല്ല!
-Mayday! Mayday! -Give it up. No one can hear you.
11ലിര്ബബല്‍! “1210 മഠ ടില്വാ ൮9 വാല ദ്ലറ്ുല !ദ്വ..
-What? -l said, "No one can hear you.”
൧്പാമ?
-He said, "No one can..."
്വാമ? 212 ൯൭൪ "ന൭ഠി൭ ടില്വാദാഠല്‍..”
Shush! Will you be quiet?
8ഠിലി ദിലമ്ധ റിസ്‌
Woody! You're back!
൧70൦0൮ (൨ ൭0 ധി!
Stop him! Don't let him get out!
1-1 :1:111 11:11 111111 11:18
Star Command! I've been taken hostage by my own prisoners.
ട്‌ ഠഠണനാഥഠി! ലിവ ഠ1മഠ॥ന്ഥ ലാധടമ്ഥ ഠിലവാമറഠ്ധമറ മിവ ടലി
Quick! Open his back. There's a switch!
ലാമ 8൭ ലാലല ഠ1൭.. ൧03 ടധിട!
Unhand me, Zurg scum!
1ലാദടിയ്ഥ മിവ, ലവ്‌ 2!
The Galactic Courts will show you no mercy.
1: 111:1111:111:1:11:1-ി 'ലിറി്ഥിരടിമ്ന ത്വ...
It's not working. Why is it not working? Where's the manual?
1൩൭ ലിധാലസ്ധഥട!.. ല്വാ മ ലിം ാല്ധാടി? സീമനാധി്വ ഉമറ്ധമ്മ?
Here we go! There should be a little hole under the switch.
ബി ഠി! ൧൭ ടാഡ 1ധാമറ9 ൭൦ ദവാ ടധ്ടാധ്മാ ടല ടലസ്ധിമ..
-Little hole, got it! -"To reset your Buzz Lightyear,
1ധീാമ0റി ൭൦... 950 ലാമി!
-"insert paperclip...” -Rex, use your finger!
പ്ഥീമടധിറ്മ് ന്യാ 1ശ൭..” 8൦% ദധി ഥി!
-Okay, now what? -All right, let's see.
ടലി ല്വാമ? ശൃഡി, 10൭.
“Caution. Do not hold button for more than five seconds."
൧ഗമട.. പാന നണടാനാാധ്മണാ ലാ। റ്‌ി 5 ടമ
It's not my fault!
ബര ലാധിത്ഥ ടമ ലിഡ്‌
Star Log...
8ധിവ ൦9 ട്വ...
I've awakened from hyper-sleep on a strange planet.
൧ിവ ലല ലടലഠ്ല ദ്മ്ലി ിഠ്ധ പാല ഠി ലിയാ നല
-Now what did you do? -[ just did what you told me!
ടന മാ ൨ 1മിഡിത്ന? വാമ മിയിത്ഥ ല്വാ ദ ദ്ധ ട്വ
I'm surrounded by alien creatures of unknown intent.
ചവ ഠ॥ലഡസ്ധബ്‌ നലിമ്പ്ധിടട്നാ ൮9 0ഠ്ദ0ി॥ശ്ധി ഡ്മ
Who goes there?
ട്രല്വാമ ഠി ടമ്മ?
Friend?
ദ്ധ?
Or foe?
൧ സ്ധടധ്?
Amigos! We're all amigos.
(ധാമ! [പര ടലസ്ധമ ഗ്മ യധമ..
I must have crash-landed and had my memory erased.
എവ ലഡഡ ലി ണ്മ ര്‍്ണ നല്ലവ ദമ ണന ലിവ റ്ലാദഠ്മബിത്ഥ
Anyone seen my spaceship?
൧.03 ടലടിമ്യാട ഒമ്പാമ ശ്വാഠി മ0ഠ1ര൭ടാ മിവ?
We gotta switch him back.
[പമ ണനടടി ഡിയിത്ഥ ഠി 1021൦.
-Well, how do we do that? -I don't know. That part's in Spanish.
ദാറുല്‌?
We don't have time for this. Come on, El Buzzo.
[പമ മഠ നട ധിധ്ബി.. ഡി, 5 8ധമമഠ!
My spaceship? You know where it is?
ര്യാമി മഥറിമടാമ മധ? ദ്ധ ഡമി ണമ?
Excellent!
ലാമി
Good luck, cowboy.
ടലണഠ93 ലാലു, ലാ...
Here they come.
1ധ റിദ നലല ദല...
Come on, Buzz!
എഡി, ദധമമ!
What took you so long?
1ലദ്വാ ദ്ധ മമ്പാ॥ നട ണമ?
Things got complicated. Where's Potato Head?
1ലാഠ്മമ [ഠി ബ്ബ... സീമ 0 11ലമഠി?
We haven't seen him.
ബി മ0ല്പാലിം ഠി1ഒ..
My desert flower!
ധന ലാദഠ്മന9 0351 മിഡി!
I have never seen true beauty until this night!
ചിവലാല്ധനലാലനമ 1102 1േബിത്ഥ മട ടല നമ്മ ബി!
Did you fix Buzz?
ദ്ധ ദ്ഖ്വ്യാണലിറി ധമ്മ?
-Sort of. -Behind you.
-1ലാ।1ഡമററ.. -210ലലററ ൨..
Someone's coming.
൧03 0309 റാ!
You would not believe what I've been through tonight.
ദ്ധ മിദത്ബ്വാലമയേ ഖാ മിധല്ധ്‌ നമിമന ബ്‌
Darling! Are you okay?
ടൃ! ദ്ധ ൦ ലാമപ്യാമ?
I feel fresh. Healthy. It's terrible.
ചവ ടെ ടലാല.. 510൭. ൭ ലഡിഠ
You've lost weight. And so tall.
8ലയ്ലാഠ്ദ ദ്ധ ഠ്ലിഡഥഡ. ഉബാലററവ നാഠ9..
You're a sight for detachable eyes.
൧... (ദ്ധ ബ്‌ നനമനാ മ്േബിം ദവാ നാമ ഠി ല്ബ്പര്ഥ
All clear.
ടലസ്ഡാബമ ടല്മണമ'..
Come on. Come on.
ലാമ. ഠലാദധി
We're almost there.
[പ്ര റമ ഖബ്വാ॥ ടമ്വാലി..
Back up. Back up!
8ലഡഥഠ്ധ.. ദല
Come on.
1 ലിവ...
Come with me!
1-1]
I will show you the wonders of the galaxy...
ചവ ലിദ്ഥ ഡബ്ധിദ്ലിര്ധ ലീലാ ല്ലി...
..and we shall vanquish all evil with our love!
൭0 10 ലിദ്ഥ ഡസൌടടിത്ഥ ടലി ഘദമഥ ഠി ന്മാസ്ല്
Come on. We're almost there.
എൃഡധി.. അ റ ലന്വാ॥ ടമമ്വാലി
The Cowboy!
1ലാഠ॥!
Buzz, come here. Give me a lift.
ധമമ, നമി ടബ്‌... ൧൭ ല്ഡ്‌
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
.8ഖമമ 111൫൨൮ലല മിദ്വഥ ടല്മണമ്ിതബല്‍്‌
It is open.
19 ലാധിര.
Way to go, Buzz. Come on.
ലാമ, 8ധമമ.. വവ
-Is it safe? -I guess I'll find out.
ഠ്യ ടല വ ടാ മിവ ല്ദ്ഥവ്ധ്ബര
-Woody? You okay? -Yeah.
“77ഠഠഠ്൮? (മല ൭ ല്വാ-ദ്യാമ? ൭...
Come on down. But not all at once.
എഡി ധ്ധബ നല ാധിത്ഥ ടലി! 90ട..
-What did he say? -I think he said, "All at once."
്വാഠ൮9 01൭ ദവിദ്വാ? വ ടാ ഠി യമ "ടലി ദ്രട്‌..
Thanks, Jess.
ലിനാ മട, പീലടട..
Where's my spaceship?
സീ ദ്വാലി ാരടമ മിവ?
Almost there, guys.
വാ ഠ്ടമനാ, ദ്ധ ൦09
Slink, you think you can make it?
ടി ബ്ത്ധ ടട ന്ധ ാംില്ഡാല്ദയമ?
Well, I might be old, but I still got a spring in my step.
ചവ സ്ഥി ഡാ ഘ്വാ! ലവ നടി 1൭91 നലബി॥ദ ടന്ന ലിവ
-He did it! -All right, Slinkykins.
21 ലാലി]ഖ്വയ! -831109, ടബവിന്നട..
Okay, climb across.
8100, ടി മിവ...
You lost, little doggie?
ദ്ധ ടട, ബനാ 1൭൦127
Well, well. Look who's back.
110മരിമ ടില്വാ ൮9 ൭൩ 1ലമ്ബാദ!..
I'm sorry, cowboy.
സീമലിധഥ മിവ, ഠ10൦!..
They broke me.
1 1-11111-11:11:11॥
What are y'all doing? Running back to your kid?
൧3൮9 സ്വ ടലസ്ധാ ദ്ഡിര്ഥ? 190 ാഠി॥വാഠഠ്മാധ്മ്ലഷസ്ധ?
He don't want you no more.
൧ ലിധനാ്ബത്ലരയസ്ധ..
-That's a lie. -Is it?
൮ ടമ ാല്വാധമ.. ട്ര?
Tell me this, Sheriff.
ലിമ മിവ ല്‍, ടല...
If your kid loves you so much, why is he leaving?
ദ്രിദ്ധവാധഠ്ല്ലത്വ ടാ ടമ്മി വധ, ഗലാദ 1൭ നല്ധാലയി?
You think you're special, cowboy?
ര്്ധ 003 ര്ധ ബി ടന ശ്വാ?
You're a piece of plastic. You were made to be thrown away.
ദ്ധ ടലഷ്വാന9 01൭50൦. ദ്ധ ഠി॥ധധിധി॥ധമഥാ
Speak of the devil.
ലാമ വാമഠ്ദ നട ബ൭..
Now, we need toys in our Caterpillar Room
ടിന, 0 ാലിധിത്ാല്ാ നമ ഠി 8॥॥ധിലഥടെട..
and you need to avoid that truck.
ഉമബദ്ധ ാലിധ ലീല ഞആചി്ലയ
Why don't you come on back, join our family again?
൧3 ൪൭ ദ്വാമ॥ ടലി ല്ധലാഠ യ്‌ ടലി! ൭17?
This isn't a family! It's a prison! You're a liar and a bully!
ബിവാധിത്ഥ 1 ഷ്ധമാല! ബര ലാല്ല വ ടല ല്വ്ാധ ദ്ദബാധി!!!
And I'd rather rot in this dumpster than join any family of yours!
മഥ മിവ ലാലല ബ്പടി ര്‍്ല്മണ ടബ്പാമ0 ബി.
Jessie's right! Authority should derive from the consent of the governed,
8ലഡി ലിയഷ്വാ പടടടില്‍!
not from the threat of force.
ഒധിത്ഥ ലി മേന നലാാേന്ലിത്ന വാടദ
If that's what you want.
ദ്രിദ്ധധവദ്ധ നലം.
Barbie! Wait! Don't do this, Lotso.
ഒല സ്ഥാ പ്‌ ാധാംറ്ബ്‌ ടം
She's a Barbie doll, Ken. There's a hundred million just like her.
1 ലാമധനറ ദാ, ൭൨.. ൧03 ലാലമഡട്ധ ട്രാ റിദ
Not to me, there's not.
8ധിത്ബാഠറ്ദ മിവ, ൭ ഠി...
Fine. Then why don't you join her!
ഒചിറ്മ്ബ ദ്രിദ്ധാല്റിഡ ലാ രര ദ്ധ ടലി ഠിച്‌
Everyone, listen!
ടലസ്ധാ 20, ലോധ
Sunnyside could be cool and groovy if we treated each other fair.
ട്ഖസുടിദ്ലാഠില്‍ [ഠി ലാമ രിദ്ധിന്മ പൃതബി ടമഡ ടണട ൭0 ൦ 3ഠി॥
It's Lotso. He's made us into a pyramid,
1൩൭ ഠ01ട൦.. ൧15 [201൭0 1൫൯ ലി.
and he put himself on top!
[11111111 1111111111:
Anyone concur with Ken?
൧.0൭ ടലടിമ്വാ 9 ടലഡ്ധ ൦1൦?
I didn't throw you away. Your kid did.
ചവ മി്ധാധമിത്സത്ധ. ഒധദ്മ്ലശ്ധവ ലഡു
Ain't one kid ever loved a toy, really.
1210 ഠ്ദാധദ്ദ്റയ ടലാലബ്ുമ ടമ്മി ന്നു
Chew on that when you're at the dump.
ന്ന 011൭ ര്ധ ാലമഠ്ദ റിന്ന ട്പാദ
Wait! What about Daisy?
1 ധാാധ! ദാാല്നമട ൦0 ലട
I don't know what you're talking about.
ചവ മയ്ഡ ലാമ ത്വ ദദ്വിര്..
Daisy? You used to do everything with her?
.൧ദ്ിടു? രവ ടലദ്ധ ലിഡിത്ഥ ടമ്മ ബിമ?
-Yeah? Then she threw us out. -No.
ര? 1ലസ്ധഠിദറ ഠി വാധ്വ ല്ധല.
-She lost you. -She replaced us!
212 ൪വിണാമത്ധ ൧19 റാണിര്ഥ മ്പി!
She replaced you.
൧൭ ദബിത്ഥ ത്വ...
And if you couldn't have her then no one could.
ഉറ വ്ി്ധ ദ്ധ മാ നലമ്പി॥ിസ്സതം ലി ാഠ്ദ ടമ്മ 9 ാഠ1ലല്‍..
You lied to Big Baby and you've been lying ever since.
ദ്ധ നല്ബ്വാധ 319 8 ദമ ദ്ധ ല൭൩൫ നല്ബ്വാധ ടല്ല്ലധ
-Where'd you get that? -She loved you, Lotso.
പഥി ദ്ധ ഠ്ഖ്ാമധ? 212 ടിന ത്വ...
She never loved me.
൧9 ലിധാലനമ ടദയ൭നാത്ഥ മിവ..
As much as any kid ever loved a toy.
ടലാമബതിം നമ ടലം09 വാധഠ്മി ടയറിന്‌ ടലാധമി ണമി
Mama.
1-1
What? You want your mommy back?
൧൧3? [ദ്ധ നമ ണമിലമ്ധ ിഷ്പാലി॥?
She never loved you. Don't be such a baby!
൧9 ലിധാലനമ ടമ്മാ ര്ധ.. പറ്്1മരിവാമ്‌!
Push ‘em in. All of ‘em!
ീമടടധിറിന നലലര ൪ റ്ലിമണ.. 1ടടെലസ്ധഃ ദ്ധി നലല!
This is what happens when you dummies try to think.
11:11: 1-1: 11:11 11111 ൮9 1ഠ0ഠ01൨ ധോ ലാഹി
We're all just trash, waiting to be thrown away! That's all a toy is!
[പ്ര ടലസ്ധമ 0ബ൭ ടബ്വാമം
Hey, stop it! Put me down, you idiot!
ദിലി! സബിത്ഥ ലിവ, ഠഠ്൦ബ
No! No! Wait a minute! Big Baby, wait!
റ്റ ന്്ച്റ സ്ഥാ ഷ്ല്ാ! വറ ലാലാ, ഡാ
-He's gone! -Holy cow.
-212 റാലി! ഛി ണനമി!
Come on. Hurry!
[7 ലാമ
For crying out loud!
ചിന.
Cowboy, hurry!
1%ഠഠ॥, ലോ
Oh, boy. Incoming!
൨, മമമ. ടലഠ്മണാ ദ്യ!
Come on!
ലാമ
Barbie, no!
1811-11-19
Can you hear me? Is everyone okay?
ദ്ധ ാഠിലറ ഠ്ലറുല മിവ? ടലസ്ഡാ 09 ടല്മണമറ
Of course not, you imbecile. We're doomed!
ടലഠിമ ഗഡ 0ിഠ്മ്പോംഠ്ംവ! പ്ര ലിദ്ഥ സ്വടമ്വ
Everyone, go to Buzz. Come on.
ടലസ്ഡാ ൦09, ലററ! ഠ്‌ 8ധമമ.. ലാമ
We all here? Slinky? Rex?
[പമ ടലസ്ധമ മഠ്ഠ ഠിട്ലി? ടബ്‌? മല
Against the wall, everybody. Quick!
ടഥറില മട റ്‌, ടലസ്ധമ ൦മ0ാ.. ലാമ
Miss! Where are you?!
.1൨ര്ധ റിന്ന?
They'll never make it!
[1:11 81:11
Look out!
1120-02!
-Anyone see him? -Over here, y'all. ! found him.
൧.0൭ ടലടിമ്യാ മ്പാമിറ റി?
Buzz, you okay?
8ധമമ, യവ ഖി ല്വാമ-ല്ാമ?
That wasn't me, was it?
1ധവാധിത്ഥ മിവ, രഥ?
Buzz, you're back! You're back, you're back, you're back, you're back!
0൩ 8ധമാ, ദ്ധ ഠ൩1ഷമ്ബാ॥॥! ദ്ധ 2൩ 1മ്ബാ॥, ത്വ 50൨ 1മ്ബവാല!!
Yes, I'm back. Where have I been?
൭, മിവ ദ്ദ ലാധിമ9.. വ്വ നമ്മ?
Beyond infinity, Space Ranger.
ലബ്ബ, അലവ്ല ൧091൪൭5൭.
Woody! So where are we now?
[പ്ര റിമ ടലദ്മ?
In a garbage truck on the way to the dump!
ഉലിമണ ആ ടമ്പാമ ദിന ലിലി 1൭ ലസ്പാമ ടമ്പാമ്വ
Hold on, we're going in!
1 ധാഠധ.. 0൭ മിദ്ഥ ണട്‌
You got all your pieces?
ദ്ധ ൭1 റില്വാമിദ്ഥ ടലന്ധമ വാമി ബിര്ധാ?
The claw!
1ല്രിവ..
-My babies! -Hey, guys! No! No!
80-00 മിഡി! ലി ദ്ധ ൦0൮! നി നിദ്ചേറ
Hang on!
ഉലുവാ
Woody! What do we do?
൧3൮9 10൭ നലിലാധാറ
We'll be okay if we stay togeth...
[പ്ര ലിദ്ഥ ടല്ദണവ്ിദ്ധ ന രാലടമനാ..
It's a magnet! Watch out!
1൩൭ ടലാധലി നാണ്‌ ൨൭01-൭0
Don't worry, Slink, we'll get you down.
പട്ന ല്ടദ്ധ, ടിം ബി മിഥ ഡധബ്ത്തിര്ധ
You might wanna take a look at this.
ദ്ധ സ്ധററിന്ന നല്ലി...
Quick! Grab something metal!
ലാമ ലററ ടടടധമവ ൮9 112 ദ്‌ ാടട!
You heard the guy.
ദ്ധ ഠാ ദിത്വാ ഠി॥൭..
It's not working!
1൩൭ ലിധാലിഗശടമ്‌
Help! Help me. I'm stuck!
101൦0൭! 7൦൦ ഖിവ..! ൧ിവ ഠി ല്ാല്ഥായാ!
Help, please! Help!
101൦0൭, 01009! 7൦1൦9!
-Thank you. -Don't thank me yet.
ലിന 1൭ട॥൨..
Go, go!
ല॥, ലാലി!
Thank you, Sheriff.
ലിനാ ര൭ട, ടല...
We're all in this together.
[വമ ടലസ്ധമലാലമഠ്ദ ഠി ബ്‌ലാലടണമ
Right, guys?
ധി, മഗ്ഗ്‌?
Guys?
ദധി?
Woody! Down here!
വാമ ടിബി!
Woody, look. I can see daylight.
177000, 1110൭... മിവ ാഠില്‍ 0൩2 ലേ ടി
We're gonna be okay!
[പ്ര ലിദ്ഥ ടല്ദണാ്‌
I don't think that's daylight.
ചവ ടാ മഠ മേമൃയര ടി
Run!
10!
Sheriff! The button! Help me!
ടലി 8ധമററ ധ്‌! 7൦൦ മഡ്‌
Come on!
7!
Go. Go! Hit the button!
ലു!.. ലാമ 7ലിബാധമറ ധ്‌
Hurry!
ലാമ
-Just push it! Push it! -Push it!
ലര ടല്യമ.. "ലിര്ബ്ബല്‍! ലിയ!
Where's your kid now, Sheriff?
നീ ാധ്ട്ലമ്ധ ടല്ഷ്ു, ലന്‌?
Buzz! What do we do?
.8ഖമമ! ഷ്യ ൮9 10൭ നലിലാധറ
The claw.
1്രിവഡധ..
You know all that bad stuff I said about Andy's attic?
ദ്ധ മ്ഡ ടലസ്ധമാലിത്മമാധി: ൮9 മിവ രലര്ഥ ധാ ൦ ൧ഡഗര്?
I take it all back.
ചവ മ്പി 1ല്പാദ!!..
-You're darn tootin’. -You said it.
1ര്്ധലാല്ധ്‌.. -ഒലധി!
Oh, darling. You were so brave.
൨, ടമ൭നാ൭.. ദ്ധ ാലറ്റ്ഡ ലാല്‌
-You saved our lives. -And we are eternally grateful.
ദ്ധ ടല്ദമനാിദ്ഥ ബമഗ യബി..
My boys!
ല്ല ലിഡ്‌
Daddy!
൧൮൭൨..
Hey! Where's that fur ball Lotso?
ലി! ശീമ ടി ടം, ാഠ1മാധ്ധധ?
Yeah. I'd like to loosen his stitchin’.
൫൭.. ചവ നാബിംഹദ്േര്ബ്മവ്മ ഠി
Forget it, guys. He's not worth it.
[ധ്യാ വധ ൦൭൧൭.. ൧9 'ഖിലാലലാമലിം!
-Hey! -What you got?
ലി! ഗ്വാ ൮9 വ്വ ഠ്ല്വാ
I had me one of these when I was a kid.
ചവ നലമ്പാഥബി ടലി ടവ ദിലി ബി നടാ മിവ 1൭൦
Strawberries.
ടനാഗാലി..
Hey, buddy. You might wanna keep your mouth shut.
ലി, മഡ്മറ..! ദ്ധ സ്ധററിന്ന നലിഡധഡാ ന്ധ്ഥിര്ധ
Come on, Woody. We gotta get you home.
കൃഡധി, ഗം... [പമ ണടട ലാമ ത്വ ാധിദ
-That's right, college boy. -Wait.
ഒല ധ, ്ധഠ്ദ്ലരിലല്‍.. “ററ.
What about you guys? I mean,
ദാവ്നാനാ ബദ്ധ മ? സീമിദ്ധഠി മിവ,
maybe the attic's not such a great idea.
ന്ധററിന്ന ൦൦00 വധി ടമഡ 1ഠ്ലേദ ൮9 ാലറ്റ്ഡ ലാ
-We're Andy's toys, Woody. -We'll be there for him, together.
പ്ര ബി നമ്നറ ൧൧൦, ഗ൦ംഠഠ..
-[ just hope he hasn't left yet. -Wait a minute!
വ ബര ല്വാ ഠിദലാല്ധന ലി 99 811: 1:11)
Wait, I'll check!
ധാ... വ്വ മിഥ ലാലിടമ!
Andy's still packing. But he's almost done!
൧൧൦൮ നടി ാലിണമട.. ലവ റി ൭0 ലമ്പാ॥ ടലിടടലി!
-He lives halfway across town. -We'll never get there in time!
2111 11:1:1:111:1111 1-111-11:
-Come on, Buster. -Is that it, honey? You got everything?
്ഥീ്ി ടിബി, രധമബ്‌ ചൃഡ, 3ധട്‌ല... ിര്ധ 51 റ്ല്വാിദ്ഥ ഭടലസ്ധമബത?
Yeah. Just a few more boxes - In my room.
൭. 11 ബര ലാലാലദ്വാ രല! ന ॥॥॥॥ലിവ
Okay. Come on.
ഷഡി, ലാല.
That's enough. That's enough. That's enough!
[1 1:11:11111
All right. Go. Go, go!
8110൭൨.. 0ലറ॥, ലാലി!
Okay. All clear.
810൭൩ 1൩൭ ടലമണമ.. 8ധിധപാധിവ ൦൭൦ല..
There you are.
രാധ ത്വ... 1 ഠി..!
-This isn't goodbye. -Hey, Woody. Have fun at college.
“ബി ലാധിത്ഥ ധല്വോമ ടലമണമ നാല്‍ ലി, ഗ്‌ഠഠഠ൮.. 8ലടലഠ0ഠ10 ഠി രില്‍...
Yeah, but not too much fun.
൮൭.. ഖി [നാമ ലില്ധാലടലംന
-Woody, take care of Andy. -Yeah.
“77000൮, [9൭1൭൨ ൧൧൨ ൭...
He's a good kid. Tell him to get a haircut.
ഉ ാധദ്ദ്ധാലി. ടയ ഠി 0090 ബ്ബാധ
Sure thing.
[111111
Jessie, you'll be okay in the attic?
പ്ലടടില, വധ ലിറിത്ഥ മ്വാമ-ഖ്വാ റി ലററ?
‘Course I will. Besides, 1 know about
ടറി ബഡ മിവവാലി. 19 ലാധന, മിവ മധ
-Buzz's Spanish mode. -My what?
റ്റ നഠഠ്‌ ടലാബ൦! 8ഖമമ 8ധിവ-8ഒധിവ ്വാമ?
Honey, you want some food for the road?
ടൃ, ത്വ ലിം നല്ല ധിധാല്ദ്മാബര്ധ?
I'll get something on the way.
1ഠലറ
You know where to find us, cowboy.
ദ്ധ ്ഡ നമ ഖി ലേ ന്അ൯, 0൦..
Did you say goodbye to Molly?
ദ്ധ ൭൨ ധല്ലോത്ഥ ടല്മനര്‍നാഠ! ാഠ്ദ ഴീഠ്?
Mom, we've said goodbye like 10 times.
ീമിലയ്ി ദ്ദ ധല്വലോദ്ഥ ടല നമ 0 ദിന 101൨
Mon, it's okay.
ീചി്പ്ൃദനാമഥ റ്ടദ്ധ മില...
I know. It's just...
ചവ മ്ഡ! ബഭ൭ ൫മ൬൫൭..
I wish I could always be with you.
വ ല്വാ മിവ ലാല ടലിടടമലാലടാണമ ദ്ധ
You will be, Mom.
സിലണമനാ ഥന, നമി.
Hey, aren't you gonna say goodbye to Buster?
ദ്ധ ഖലം ധല്ലോത്ഥ ടലി്മണമ നാല്‍ ാഠ്ദ 8ഒഖട്‌ല?
Of course I am. Who's a good doggy?
ടറി ബഡ.. ട്ലാഠ മലനാ ലി
Who's a good doggy? I'm gonna miss you. I'm gonna miss you.
ടരല്വാദ ബനാ ലാലിറ ഷിവ ലിത്ഥ 10ഠ്ധിത്ബന്ധ.. ചവ മിത്ഥ ഗ്നധിത്സിത്ഥ!
-I'm gonna miss you. -Don't, Andy.
വ മിത്ഥ ഗ്നര്‍്ധിത്ബിത്ധ. നറു...
Good boy. He's telling you to go already.
൧ വാദലട.. 1൭ 21 ടധഡ്സിശ്ധ ലാലാ.
Come on. Get the rest of your things.
ഉല്പാദ്ധിദ്ബാദലിനാലാറ ന്ധ
Okay, Buster. Now don't let Molly near my stuff.
810൭൨ 3ഒധട്ല ടിനാവയബ്ബോമമ്ലിത്ഥ നീം ഠ്ലിര്ധി ലാമ മിവ
Hey.
ല്‍... നമിറ
Hey, Mom! So, you really think I should donate these?
പി9ഠി!.. നമിധടമ മിവ മഡട ഠ്ലനലിത്ഥ നല ബി?
It's up to you, honey. Whatever you wanna do.
1ല്ാധിററ ാഠ്ദ ദ്ധ, ടാ! ൧3 ട്വ ദ്ധ 0ലിലാധ
“Don't go in there! The bakery is haunted!"
1: 11:1:111111:111 11:11:11-111:1 8ചിഘി ഡലാലണമബ്ധ്‌
“Are you crazy? You'll wake up all the ghosts.”
ദ്ര്ധ 0 91? ദ്ധ മിദബാഗബ്ത്ഥ ടല്ഡാ മ൧൩൮..
“Look out! The ghosts are throwing pies!"
1120-00! 11 ട൦ലഠ്ദറ9 നലം വാല!
Mom.
1-1
Wow. Look at you.
110മ്ിമ ഠി വധ...
Well, I hear you're off to college.
ചവ റിബാ ദ്വ ലിര്ഥ ദ രില്‌
Yeah. Right now, actually.
൭. ടലിദ്ധമു, ടലാലണു..
So, what can we do for you?
പി9ഠി, ലാമ ൮9 യി വാല ലിഡിത്ഥ ധലര്ധ?
I have some toys here.
ചവ നലമ്പാഥബതി ാലാലല്വാ നമ്മ ഠി ടബ്‌
You hear that, Bonnie?
ദ്ധ ലാല, ദംബ്ബ്ല?
So, you're Bonnie?
പ്മഠി॥, ദ്ധ 8ംലബ്ല?
I'm Andy.
ചവ ൧ഥഠ..
Someone told me you're really good with toys.
൧03 009 ാലിദ്ച്ഡ മിവ ദ്ധ ാറഠില ഒറ നമ്നഥ
These are mine, but I'm going away now,
ബി സ ലിവ 'ല്വാി മിവ നമ്ലാലഠ! ടല്‍൭൭ഥ൭..
so 1 need someone really special to play with them.
പഠി മിവ ാലിധിത്ന ടടടലം ററ ൮9 ടണാഠ്ധ്ടനണേട്കെ ധിഗനമ്റ ണേണ്ണ
This is Jessie, the roughest, toughest cowgirl in the whole West.
ബി ടടടില, യാ ഉലഘലമ്പാധാഥ യ 0300 1വടാല, ലാല്ല റ ടല്ധഡ്ിയഗടറ 8
She loves critters, but none more than her best pal, Bullseye.
൧19 ടധിര ാനമ൭ഥ൭, ദ്വ! ലലാ ദ്വി യഥാ യലാബരം, ഒധിടലുട
Here.
12൨..!
This is Rex, the meanest, most terrifying dinosaur who ever lived!
ബി ൫൦ ഠ0ഠടം വാട ലന ദമ നലാല്ഡിത്ഥ വ ലാണമ്ധ്വോ
The Potato Heads. Mr. and Mrs. You gotta keep 'em together,
ഉമടാറമന 0൦൭൦ 11ലമഠിട, 5൨. 0 0൨൩.. ദ്ധ നട്ടി ടിമ്പാമഥ ബ്0ിലാലടമണമ
‘cause they're madly in love.
ടലാലാ 0 ടിന ലന
Now Slinky here is as loyal as any dog you could want.
ട്ല്വ്ഥമറാ, ടബ്വ ബി ടടടലിമ നമഥമ-ണമാ ലന ദ്ധ നമിറത0..
And Hamm, he'll keep your money safe,
ഉമ ്ണണ, ഠി ലിദ്ഥ നലല്‍ന്ഥ്ോ! ധ്ലേര്ധ..
but he’s also one of the most dastardly villains of all time, evil Dr. Pork Chop.
ചവ റിവാ ലവ്‌ മനാ 1ഘ്മണ.. ൧. ൧൦0 ൦0൨൧0൧ 3൭ 11൭...
These little dudes are from a strange alien world.
ധ്യ്ഥാ-ം അഥ 1൭൦ ബി ദ്മ്0ി റ്ധബ്മ നല്മ്പ്ധിം ടട മല
Pizza Planet.
ലല ലമ2..
And this
ഉമ്ഥ ബി...
is Buzz Lightyear, the coolest toy ever!
1-111-12 4111-11 നമനമഥ ാമ109 ലാമി
Look, he can fly and shoot lasers!
11:11 11-11] ദ്ദ നലാലമ്പാദപ്ധടടല്‌
He's sworn to protect the galaxy from the evil Emperor Zurg.
ഉ ലാലടധന്പാമ നല്‍നഠനാ। ല്ല്ദ! [1 :111:1:11-121 11-11]
To infinity and beyond!
൭ 7077077 ന്ഥ ടല്ദ൧)൭
Now, you gotta promise to take good care of these guys.
ട്ല്വ്ഥമാ, മധ ണനടട വമി! നല്വദ9മ നലല ബ്‌ ബാലി
They mean a lot to me.
സീലല്ര ടന റാഠ്ദ മിവ...
My cowboy!
14൦ മിഡ്‌
Woody? What's he doing in there?
൧70൦01? ൧൮൮9 01100 ഠ്ച്മണ ടമ?
-"There's a snake in my boot." -Wha...?
൧03 ധി റ്മിമന രാധ ലിവ..
There's a snake in my boot.
൧ീറ്ദ ല്‌ദ റ്ദദഗ7 ൧൧ ൭൨൮...
Now, Woody, he's been my pal for as long as I can remember.
ടന, ഗ7ഠഠഠ, ഠി ഠ൭൩൮9ഠ01 ണമ്ഥ മിവ ടല മിവലാംല്‍ലനാ%
He's brave, like a cowboy should be.
൧1 ലാലയ്ബ്‌ ടലാലി നമ്മ ടല009 1101 ൫മബട [൭ഠ..
And kind. And smart.
ബാലി... ഉപാധി
But the thing that makes Woody special is he'll never give up on you.
ചാ ടാഡ ാലിവ ൮9 ാധമിത്ഥ ഗം 1ടരിനഗ്ജ ൭1൭1൨.
Ever.
ടല്ദണാബമ..
He'll be there for you, no matter what.
1൭ മിഥ നലല ദലം 'ലിധന്നു ല്വാ 0൩...
You think you can take care of him for me?
ദ്ധ ന॥ന്നലിര്ധ ലാല നല്വമമ ഠി ധം ലിയ?
Okay then.
8ചിറ്്വിരിദ്ധാല്ധ..
Oh, no! Dr. Pork Chop's attacking the haunted bakery!
൨0൭. 2. 0൦000൧ ടറി നല മിഷ ൮൭ 0ബയി!
The ghosts are getting away. Woody'll stop ‘em!
110 ടല നല്ലി ഠി... 77000 മമ ണലറന്റ്മിമറ്0ിറ്‌
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
.8ഖമമ 1101൫൨ മിദ്ഥ നലഘല്ണമിത്ല്‍്‌
And we'll actually need the rocket.
ഉമ്മ മിര നലനലിധിത്ഥ 701൪൭.
They're getting away! Come on, Bullseye!
സീലല്ര ടലഠ്ദണാ നല്ലാടടിര്ഥ റല! എഡ, ദധിടലല്‍
We need to get in the spaceship. The volcano is gonna erupt.
[പ്രമ ാല്ധ നടടധി റിന ദ്വാമി 50൨91൨൭5൭.. ഠം ലിദ്ഥ നല്ല്ഡാ
Look! They're being attacked by a real dog!
സില്ലി ടലഠ്മണാ ഠിടലറ ഠ1ല൨ ബന ടലാലഘല്‌!
You can eat my poisonous scones!
ദ്ധ ാഠ1ല൨ ണമി ടിഠബാലമധേറ മിഡ്‌!
Mr. and Mrs. Potato Head are in trouble.
5൨. ഠ്മ ൩. 002൦ 11ലമ്‌ ാലമഠ്ദ റ്മിമണ്വാമ്മയര
Get on, Woody.
കൃഡി, ഗ്‌൦൦ദ..!
It's my friend Woody.
1൩൭ രഥ മിവ, 77ഠ൦ഠഠ1..
Buzz, hurry! Get your extra turbo booster.
8ധമമ, ലോ ച്വാിദ്ഥ ഡാം 0ഠഠട്്‌ല ദ്ധ ൮9 ലാലിലാ।മ്ഥ
Thanks, guys.
ലിന 1൭ടി൨ത്ധ ംമ0ാ..
Look, Mommy. They're all playing together.
1103 നലം. സില്ലി ടലി ാല്നല്ബാലടമണമ
Come on. Let's get some lunch.
എഡി, ലോമിത്ഥ നലിര്ഥമഥ 2൭0 0൫൨..
So long, partner.
ടല നാഠമ, ൦൭൨.
Hey, Buzz. You haven't met Bonnie's toys yet. Hey, come here.
൨൨൫0ല്‍ 8ഖമാ.. ((ധ്ധാല്ധമ്പ്ഥ്വാദ നമി 8ംബ്ല 1൭91 നീലി ടിബി.
You're gonna love them. Buzz, this is Dolly.
ദ്രധ മിഥ ടധിയിരഥ ബ്ല, ധമ്മ, ബി ൧൦॥..
New toys!
ീല്നമബാലഡ്‌
Noses.
1009...
“So Il guess you could say Sunnyside is sunny once again!
പ്9ഠി। മിവ ടമ ദ്ധാംില്‍ രവിര്ഥ ൮ ടധടിര്‍്ടേ ദ്ദ ലോ ടലസ്ഡില
“Hope to hear from you soon. We're all super excited about your new home.
ല്ലാ റ്ല്വാമനലാല റ്‌ി സ്ധ മില്ലനട 1മ91..
“Hugs and kisses to everyone."
ഉല്ധിത്ഥ ദമ വധണമ്ഥ 0909 ടലന്ധാ ൦09
That Barbie has some nice handwriting.
1 ധിടാറ ദഒദ്ലില ദേ.
Buzz, Barbie didn't write this.
ഒബി മ0ണല്ഡിബമ
-Grab the sword! -I got it!
എല്വാദ്ധിദ്ഥ ലാലാ! വ ദ്ദ ദ്ദ്യാദിര്ബയ!
-Okay, go for the... -Triple bonus!
൧ല്വാദിഥ.. -8ഠബ്വട 3 1
-Watch out! -We got the cloak of darkness!
1190-00! 11 ൭0 ്വ്രാദധിയബ്വധാമ ലുലദ്പാമബ്‌
-Run, run! -My arms are never long enough!
1901! “ഗാന മിവ മ ധിയ്വലാമബനറ!
I'll do it! This is it! This is it!
ചവ ലിദ്ഥില്വഡിര്ുത! ബി ദ! ബി ദില
-Yes! -We did it!
ട്‌ി 1 ടമ൨ലിഡ്രണബ൭!
High-five! Hold on.
ലാധിദഥ 1191-ല്‍ സ്ഥാ9॥..!
Well, it's official. You guys made the wall.
1൩൭ ച മടമ്പ്‌. ദ്ധ ൦09 ടമമ്പാലി ൪ റിന്ന
-Look at this! -Golly bob howdy! That's me!
ബ്‌ ലിവ്‌! നമ. ധ ലിയ
We're all up here! Hey, Chuckles, lookin’ good.
[പ്ര ടലസ്ധമ ഠി മട ടലി! റല ്ധടട, നസ്വാമിലാമട..
Yeah, she really got your smile.
൭, ദി നല്ധിട ടപബൃധണമന ദ്ധ ര്‍്്ബാലിം
I told you kids! Stay out of my butt!
ചവ റ്മ്വാലിയ്ഡിത്ധ ന! 1-1 ::111:11811:11111:11111:1:10
But soft, what light through yonder window breaks?
ച്ാ। ലമ്പാധ്‌, ലോ ല്വാദ ൮9 നണമറലേ ഠി വ്വ ഠി ടമ?
Romeo, o Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?
൫൪0൩൦൦, ൦ ൯0നലഠ, നമ്മ ദ്ധ ൯ഠനലഠ?
Next season, we're doing Cats.
ിീധട്ന ടലലഡടബമം, ഗ്മ മിഥ മിഡിത്ഥ ൦ഒട..
Or might I suggest Hamlet?
൧൨ സ്ധനഠിന്ന മിവ ദേര ഥ്ദസം?
Yeah. Detached wing. Cosmetic damage.
ടമൃത്വാ ദ 0൭൭൨.. ലംടമിമറരടണലി.
Nothing a little duct tape can't fix.
121 റിദ മ്വാ ൮9 0119 ലാലില്‍ 'ലിധാംില്ഡാലിര
I don't know what came over me.
ചവ മമ്ഡ ഖാ ൦90 ാഠ്ദ മിവ
Just go with it, Buzz.
ഡ്‌ ടദ്യദ 8ധമമ..